(This program may contain indirect advertisements.)
(Running Man)
- Hello. - Hi.
- Hello. - Okay!
(At the end of August, as the heat begins to ease...)
Hello!
(The members have gathered at a cafe.)
- Hello. - Congratulations, Jong Kook!
- Congratulations on your concert! - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
(Jong Kook had his 30th-anniversary concert the night before the shoot.)
- Congratulate what? - Congratulations on your concert!
- Congratulate what? - Hello.
- Hello. - Thank you.
- Hello. - All right.
- Congratulations on your concert. - Hello.
(He greets those who attended his concert like a newlywed groom.)
Thank you for taking the time to come.
- His concert was amazing. - Thank you, Se Chan.
(Lots of love)
- Thank you for coming. - It's my pleasure.
(Three no-shows)
- Thanks. - Congratulations on your concert.
- Didn't you go? - Stay quiet.
- Go away. - Go!
(He hurls the one that didn't attend.)
How dare you talk to us?
- I'm sorry. - He didn't invite us,
(The three attendees are full of confidence.)
but we just showed up on our own.
We just went there voluntarily.
Jong Kook, did anyone reach out to you...
(Trying to appeal)
on the day of the concert?
They all came instead of reaching out to me.
- I guess you called him. - We just went there.
(Annoying)
Someone who was busy that day might have at least called you.
- We just went. - It's not like that.
He buttered me up so much for my investment before, but...
Oh, no.
I can still hear it ringing in my ears.
(CEO Kim brings up the business they had together 10 years ago.)
- But I had some work to do. - That's enough.
Still, I sent you a congratulatory video.
- That's enough! - All right.
Just be patient and hang in there for today.
- Right. - Take it easy today, Haha.
- He's right. - Jong Kook won't hold a grudge.
(He has nothing to say since he didn't go.)
It won't last for long.
- All right. Thank you. - He won't hold a grudge for long.
- Yes. - It won't last for too long.
Just be patient for about a week.
(Today will be a long day...)
- It's okay. - I loved your concert.
So, Jong Kook...
pulled off a live concert.
- It was awesome. - I sent you a video.
(The 30th-anniversary concert was packed with live performances.)
- It was really... - This calls for a celebration.
It was my first time seeing Seok Jin stay awake the whole time.
- I kept jumping like this. - That's true.
Seok Jin was even singing along to songs he didn't know.
I actually sang along to every single one of your songs.
(Kind)
- Really? - Yes.
- He did. - Even the songs he didn't know.
We musicians can catch the melody and sing along right away...
- even if we don't know the song. - That's true.
(Going along with everything)
So did you enjoy it? I'm glad to hear that.
Seok Jin was sitting like this with his legs crossed.
Can't you see it, hiding behind my back
(Slapping his knee)
(He sang passionately to the knee-slapping beat.)
And when you raised your arms like this...
(Flicking)
(Laughing)
- When I raised my arms? - You should raise them like this.
The vibe gap between those who showed up and didn't...
While we were like this, Seok Jin was doing this.
(The harmonious and friendly concert cartel)
- That still means a lot to me. - Of course.
(Sheepish)
- I'm just grateful. - It was really great.
(Pretending to have attended)
I couldn't go wild like this.
- I understand. - He just flicked his hands.
(The concert stories never end.)
Thank you so much.
- Congratulations on your new song! - All right.
(Let's talk about your new song!)
(Singer Kim's new song came out on August 14.)
- Your new song is coming out. - Yes.
- It's already out. - It's out.
("Let Me Hold You Just Once" written by Roy Kim went viral.)
(Jong Kook is back to his day job after 2 years and 5 months.)
- Roy Kim wrote the song. - Roy Kim.
Right. I sang it at the end of the concert.
(If you don't listen to it, Jong Kook will get sulky.)
- We watched it. - What's the rush?
Who asked that?
- And you... - All right.
Haha is also holding a concert.
("We Never Die")
- It's September 13. - There are...
- still a few tickets left. - Tickets.
Please buy some tickets!
There are still tickets left. I'm squeezing every last sale out.
- Please. - It will be fun!
- Please. - It's not just Haha.
There will be a lot of great musicians performing.
- There will be a lot. - Many good musicians?
(Send love to Haha's concert, where many guests will attend.)
- We have special guests for today. - Okay.
(There will be two guests for today's race.)
- Please come on in. - I can see them.
(The guests enter.)
- Hello. - Hello.
(Singer, Kwon Eun Bi)
- Eun Bi. - Eun Bi!
- Eun Bi. - Hello.
(Comedian, Kim Won Hun)
- Won Hun is here. - Won Hun.
- Hey, Won Hun. - Won Hun.
Assume the push-up position.
Hang on. This van is full of freeloaders.
Wait. Seok Sam, it's been a while.
- "Seok Sam." - She's not really Kwon Eun Bi...
unless she's getting soaked at the Waterbomb Festival.
And you're not really Kim Jong Kook unless you're on Gym Jong Kook.
(Running Man members' ultimate button-pusher)
Hey, I was a celebrity even before Gym Jong Kook existed.
Let's go protest outside her building.
(Resist!)
- With some banners. - Come on out, Kwon Eun Bi!
(The new tiger moth whose hobby is messing things up, Kwon Eun Bi)
Come out!
You're banned from SBS. You can't come ever again.
- All we can do now is study. - Will you study or not?
(The prince of short-form content)
(The guy with the meme, "Are you in or not?" and "It's awkward.")
- Are you in or out? - Are you in or out?
The college entrance exam is only one year away, so it's awkward.
It is awkward indeed.
The only senior colleague I truly respect is Yu Jae Seok.
(Lee Gyeong Gyu)
- Hey! How dare you? - Gyeong Gyu.
Why don't you just go film YouTube videos in Japan too?
Stop coming here and ruining our vibe.
(A comedian who puts his life on the line for laughs)
- You punk... - You guys filled in...
(Blue Dragon Series Awards winner and trending comedian, Kim Won Hun)
everywhere I felt short, so I could win this award.
- Hi. - Hello, Won Hun.
- Are you in or out? - This is my first time meeting him.
He's the one with "Are you in or out?"
- Nice to meet you. - Are you in or out?
(Happy to see him)
- All right. - This is awkward.
- Eun Bi has been here many times, - Right.
but this is Won Hun's first time.
(It's Won Hun's first time on Running Man.)
This is my first time here.
- I know. - This is your first appearance.
- It's my first time. - That's right.
So did you come here with high hopes or something?
It's not that I have high hopes, but I just want to have fun.
(Timid)
- All right. - Okay.
There are Fake Won Hun and Real Won Hun.
I have two alter egos.
- Which one will you bring out? - Go with the real one.
(Which one is he bringing out today?)
- Go with the real one. - For today, it's Real Won Hun.
- Okay. The real one. - I see.
(He will reveal the authentic Won Hun, which he never revealed.)
- It's Real Won Hun. - Go with Real Won Hun.
Be serious.
- But the real Won Hun is quite shy. - Really?
- He's very polite and shy. - He is.
These days, Won Hun is known...
(Until now, it was the fake Won Hun, who was always overdoing it.)
as the variety shows' newest overreacher.
- I see. - With his over-the-top characters.
But you're showing the real Won Hun today.
- I'm not doing any of them today. - Not today.
You won't overreach yourself today?
(What a shame.)
- It's fun. - You were curious about him, right?
(We were wanting the fake Won Hun.)
I want to show my authentic self.
(He insists on showing the shy real Won Hun today.)
Won Hun recently won...
an award at the Blue Dragon series Awards.
- Finally. - He took home a trophy.
(He won the Best Male Entertainer Award!)
Congratulations.
- He deserves it. - Congratulations.
- Congratulations. - He's really funny.
(Congratulations!)
- Finally. - Thank you.
- So, Won Hun and Ye Eun... - They must be close.
(They are very close due to "SNL" and "Office Workers.")
- You two are close, right? - They do "Office Workers."
On Thursday, Won Hun told me that he'd be joining Running Man.
"Ye Eun, I'll be on Running Man."
And he asked me to name all the gifts he'd given me.
What gifts?
- Won Hun... - She needs to say this.
(He asked her to give a shout-out on the list of gifts.)
I get her a gift for her birthday every year.
(Ye Eun does.)
- That's true. - I see.
When she said she was moving, I got her a lamp.
(At Ye Eun's house)
- She has many pretty lamps at home. - Right.
After he got me a lamp... Let me take over and list the rest.
Okay.
(That's good.)
(She starts the shout-out that Won Hun wanted.)
- I'll say it. - Go ahead.
- Chanel mist, - What?
Chanel lip balm,
a COS bag,
(Proud)
- Okay. - and a rice cooker.
- A rice cooker? - He showered you with gifts.
- He did. - Did you ask for all of them?
No. You just gave them to me.
But the thing is, Ye Eun always contacts me...
on her birthday.
"What are you doing, Won Hun?" She sends a text like this.
(Ye Eun: What are you doing?)
Then I go, "Hey."
- "I'm just doing something." - Ye Eun.
And it turns out it's her birthday.
(Perfect timing)
- Really? - It's not like that.
Because we're close, I just ask, "What are you doing?"
(She happened to be curious about him on her birthday.)
"You know it's my birthday, right?"
I also gave you gifts.
- Then you also... - I gave him gifts.
- What did you get him? - What did you get him?
A 100 percent cotton T-shirt.
- Something like this? - But...
the collar never stretches out.
- No, Won Hun. - Something like this?
(Taken aback)
I got you three pieces.
(Important)
- Three pieces? - So it's three for ten dollars.
The water absorption is so good...
- that I use it to wipe the floor. - That's because they're close.
- Right. - Because we're close.
(A friendship that's truly priceless)
- It's because we're close. - A cotton T-shirt...
Won Hun knows how to spend money.
- Right. - That's true.
- He's nice. - He's really generous.
(Gazing silently)
- He gives a lot of gifts. - You're really cool.
The way she looks at you has changed.
- Is it your birthday? - Yes. It's coming soon.
- Give me a call. - September 27.
- Just ask me what I'm doing. - What?
She says her birthday is September 27.
- I want a sock gift set. - A sock gift set?
(Specific)
- She's really brazen. - She's unbelievable.
(Her shamelessness amazes them every time.)
- She's shameless. - There's no backing down with her.
It's better to keep a safe distance from Eun Bi.
- Eun Bi is really brazen. - Jong Kook just said...
that it's better to keep a safe distance.
You shouldn't get too close to Eun Bi.
(Does he have personal experience?)
- It's called a beautiful distance. - Exactly.
I'll go to your gym in September.
(To get a gift from you)
(She needs the beautiful distance especially in September.)
Just keep it at the level where it's nice to see each other.
So, this is Won Hun's first time on Running Man.
(Unlike Won Hun, who is here for the first time...)
- Right. - And Eun Bi...
This is my seventh time.
(It's actually her sixth time. She drops by every chance she gets.)
She's been here a lot.
Are you here because your new song is coming out?
- How did you know? - It's obvious.
- That's why you came. - Your new song is coming out.
- She should do that. - Your new song is out?
(Eun Bi's new song will be released on September 3.)
It's coming out on September 3.
What's the title of your song?
It's called "Dejavu."
- "Dejavu." - "Dejavu."
Can you perform the song a little for us?
- Go ahead. - "Dejavu."
(The performance of "DEJAVU" will be showcased first here!)
- We will play the music. - Okay.
- The track... - Music, cue.
(Deja Deja Vu)
- It sounds refreshing. - It's nice.
(Dancing)
This is perfect for the Waterbomb Festival.
- It's for the Waterbomb Festival. - It is.
(The Waterbomb Festival Queen's "DEJAVU" with late summer vibes)
This is nice.
The dance is quite easy.
(The ending fairy)
As expected, this is...
(This is really nice!)
- Actually... - Anyone can easily follow along.
Actually, Eun Bi...
- debuted as a dancer. - Right.
Her dance moves are on another level.
(Eun Bi's short but impactful performance)
- They are different. - Yes.
You know what, Eun Bi?
You always show up playing all innocent,
only to backstab us at the end.
- She always betrays us. - So our feelings are a bit hurt.
- Really? - Look at Seok Sam.
- You are... - You didn't seem so thrilled...
when I showed up.
My memories of you are far from great.
(Eun Bi piled up karma every time she came here.)
He doesn't like Eun Bi.
She stole my seat on the bus,
(Stealing seats on the bus)
and she tried to save herself alone during the penalty.
(Sabotaging the punishment and escaping alone)
- You remember that, right? - Let's make up.
Forget it. I'll just see how it goes.
"Forget it. I'll just see how it goes."
(What karma will she build up today?)
We don't have many guests with such audacity.
And I heard Won Hun...
What does that mean that you prepared a song?
- Really? - He will sing.
(Did Won Hun also prepare a performance like Eun Bi?)
Do you want to sing?
- Shall I give it a try? - Sure.
(Shy)
Go ahead.
(A song sung by the real Won Hun)
Please play the instrumental track.
Did you prepare the instrumental track as well?
- What? He's fully prepared. - He prepared a lot.
(Which song did Won Hun prepare, with the MR and a microphone?)
He tries really hard.
- Since it's raining a bit today, - The weather?
so I'm singing "In the Rain."
(Secondhand embarrassment)
Since it's raining a bit today, so I'm singing "In the Rain."
- What's wrong, Se Chan? - I just like it.
Go ahead and do it.
(A song as soft as rain, prepared by the real Won Hun)
You look so cool.
(Super serious)
(Laughing)
But...
Is this for real?
Isn't this song a little too mellow for a variety opening?
- So why... - But...
(He's the first comedian to sing a ballad song in the opening.)
sometimes musicians perform songs like this here.
I'm feeling a little embarrassed for him.
- I'm embarrassed. - This is...
Go, Running Man.
There must be something in the middle.
In the rain
- He sings well. - He's good.
He is surprisingly good.
On the street
- He's good. - He sounds great.
I'm thinking
Why is he doing this during the opening anyway?
- This is the most critical moment. - Of you
- It has to be funny. - What is he going to do now?
- There will be something. - It's a buzzkill.
The unattainable love
(Immersed)
I guess we'll just have to wait and see, right?
(Jae Seok finally steps in.)
It will be funny.
I hold it deep inside my soul
(You should do something.)
(Trying to salvage the real Won Hun's performance)
All day long
(Seok Sam steps up.)
(Pushing it down)
(He rejects the helping hand.)
Standing in the rain
I'm thinking
Of you
Thinking, thinking, I'm thinking of you
"Thinking, thinking."
- Did you really have to leave - Did you really have to leave
(Big Nose's backup vocal barely revived the performance.)
(It finally feels like a proper comedian's opening performance.)
- Leaving my heart behind - Leaving my heart behind
In the pouring rain
(Glaring)
- It's raining - Like this
(Bickering)
Okay!
- The climax. - Okay. Let's go!
(Cut it out.)
- All those - All right.
(Stopped)
- That's enough. - All right.
(The stage is finally brought to a forced end.)
You should wait. There could be something.
He passed.
- He passed? - It's a pass.
This isn't about passing or failing.
Were you going to pour some water or something?
(Disappointed)
- I think that was it. - Won Hun.
(Really disappointed)
- I thought you'd do impressions. - Was that it?
- It was going to be emotional. - We waited a lot.
So there was something.
(The real Won Hun came to the wrong place.)
I prepared something fun.
- This is it for today. - It was at the end.
(Sighing)
- You stopped right before that. - It was too long.
Please give him a big hand.
(Quickly ending it)
- All right. - This is...
(Clapping)
You prepared this so seriously.
Won Hun sings quite well, anyway.
He is really good.
That's the saddest thing to hear.
- "He sings well." - He does sing well.
- I can tell you did musicals. - Yes.
(Great vocals!)
He's better than you expected.
- He's really good. - He is.
But, Won Hun, the thing is,
variety shows can't have long intros.
- But this is... - We can't do that.
I think this is what we need...
(He speaks his mind.)
- to change in variety shows. - Change what?
- I don't understand why... - Right.
comedians are expected to be funny every single time.
- Right. - But how about you change?
I think it'd be better to be funny every single time.
(They also speak their minds.)
We called you over because you were funny.
But I want to show my true self.
Okay.
Why are you sulky?
You let Eun Bi do whatever she wanted.
- But Eun Bi is good. - It can't be helped.
(Upset)
The fake Kim Won Hun is coming out.
- Right. - If I had...
- If I had a new song out... - That's enough.
(Luckily, the fake popped out as he was pushed to the edge.)
We all have our own roles here.
- My goodness. - Okay.
Today, the real Kim Won Hun...
Before we do that,
you should let me show you something.
- That's enough. - You did well.
We just move on without letting me do anything?
That was enough.
- Take it easy. - Hey.
- It's coming out again. - You have a lot of things to do.
- It's coming out again. - The shoot is long.
(Happy to see it)
I think this is funny.
(Let's keep the real Won Hun for private gatherings.)
- This is it. - Today,
we have a race inspired by Won Hun's catchphrase.
It's called Take it? Leave it?
- Take it? Leave it? - Take it? Leave it?
Since quite a few of you have August birthdays,
(Jae Seok, Ji Hyo, and Haha were born in August.)
and we're joined by two special guests today,
we've prepared a wide variety of prizes.
Depending on your choices, everything from winning prizes...
to your clocking-off time will be decided.
Okay.
Before the opening shoot,
we asked each of you whether you'd take ten dollars or not.
So that's why today's race is Take it? Leave it?
(Take it? Leave it?)
Take it? Leave it? This is it.
(Ambushing the members' vans the second they arrived at work)
Hello.
Jae Seok. Ten dollars, take it or leave it?
- What did you say? - Ten dollars, take it or leave it?
Of course I'll take it.
You chose to take ten dollars.
(Tiger Moth Jae Seok chose to take it.)
You get ten dollars right away.
- Can I keep this? - Yes.
Se Chan, take it or leave it?
Why even ask the obvious?
I'll take it.
(Along with the Protruded Tiger Moths...)
- I'll take it. - Of course I'll take it.
(Mr. Jee and Ms. Ji also chose to take it.)
Thank you.
Kim Jong Kook.
Take it or leave it?
(Blown away)
It blew away.
- Leave it? - It blew away.
Take it or leave it?
I'll leave it.
- Leave it? - Yes.
Okay.
Is this a theme or something?
- Did you say it yourself? - You chose to leave it.
(Snake eyes on)
You don't get ten dollars.
I'll see you at the opening shoot soon.
(Staring)
(After Petty Jong Kook,)
I have a bad feeling about it.
(the Mapo Siblings also chose to leave it.)
Leave it.
Kim Won Hun, take it or leave it?
(Real)
(Fake)
It feels awkward to leave it.
Take it or leave it?
- Take it or leave it? - Take it or leave it?
It feels awkward to leave it!
(Kim Won Hun chose to take it.)
I'm not even wearing my shoes.
But keeping something like this...
always causes trouble. It will backfire.
But I'll keep it for now.
I'll take it.
(Lastly, it's Eun Bi's turn.)
Ten dollars, take it or leave it?
I'll leave it.
It looks suspicious.
- Then... - I'll close the door.
(Go away.)
(Hesitating)
Should I take it?
Leave it?
But...
it looks somewhat suspicious.
(Ten dollars for free?)
I'll leave it. I'm sure.
(With Eun Bi wrapping it up, all 9 of them made their choices.)
Your choices have determined...
the teams and method for your first mission.
No way.
Those who chose to take it...
are Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Se Chan,
Ye Eun, and Won Hun.
And those who chose to leave it...
are Jong Kook, Haha, Ji Hyo, and Eun Bi.
You should take it.
- I'll reveal the result. - What is it?
Check the board for instructions.
- Ten dollars. - Please crash and burn.
- Please. - Take it or leave it.
(Ten dollars changed the fate of the two teams.)
- Crash and burn. - We chose ten dollars.
- Take it. - It'll be trash.
We chose ten dollars.
("Take it" is revealed first.)
- Take it. - It was just ten dollars.
Take it.
- Take a bus. - Take a bus.
- What? - What's this?
(Then what about "Leave it?")
- What? - That's good.
What's that?
Please!
(Take it: Take a bus, Leave it: Take a car)
- Oh, no... - Okay!
(Team Take It, Team Leave It)
- A bus... - A car is much better.
(They will be split between a bus and a car for the mission.)
Is a car the better choice?
The first team to arrive...
and claim the flag wins.
- Oh, really? - That's not easy.
- Team Take It got ten dollars. - Yes.
- Charge your transportation card... - Okay.
and use public transport.
We must do that ourselves?
- Yes. - Where can we do that?
Team Leave It will drive to the destination.
- I see. - That can be done.
- I should've chosen "leave it." - A bus...
- I didn't want to take it. - I should've said no.
- But this option... - Yes.
I've never said no.
- Right. - They offered cash.
You can give it to me.
- It's my bus fare. - Team Leave It...
Neither team can use their phones or car GPS.
- That's... - We'll give you a map.
- A map? Okay. - Use that to find your way.
- It'll show everything. - Nice.
The destination is 45 minutes away by bus...
and just 15 minutes by car.
Those taking the bus will get a more detailed map.
- Yes. We need that. - Okay.
- Sounds good. - Yes.
- Okay. - Let's go.
(Both teams get maps.)
- Map, please. - Okay.
I do tend to figure my way with a map.
They're different. We shouldn't show the others.
(Team Bus, Team Car)
- The bus team. - It's really detailed.
Don't let the others see.
(They split up and check the maps.)
Don't look. Go away.
I'm on your team.
Are you?
- I'm taking the bus. - I don't think so.
(The bus takers' map has more detail.)
- I am. I have ten dollars. - Do you?
- Deungchon-dong. - I know this place.
(Current location: cafe, Destination: outdoor stage)
Near the Deungchon-dong SBS building.
(The shortest route goes...)
Yes, it's near SBS.
(through Sangam-dong and across the bridge.)
- This way. - Hey, from here...
The used-car market...
We can take the town shuttle bus.
(Will they be able to find their way there by bus?)
Cross the road here...
and one bus ride and we're there.
Let's have a look.
(Team Car also checks the map.)
Do you know this area?
- Do you know the area? - Yes, I know the area.
- Do you? - Yes.
(Compared to Team Bus's map,)
- There's a cafe here. - Where are we going?
- Here? - Yes.
(Team Car's map has fewer landmarks on it.)
I know this place. We're right here.
I know too.
- Let's go. - Let's head out.
- We can't look it up. - Go, let's go.
(Team Car sets off.)
Hey, what a cute car.
(The car is parked right in the building's parking lot.)
- Gosh. - It's adorable.
Let's get going.
(The navigation system is sealed.)
- Eun Bi, sit up front. - Okay.
- Let's go. - Oh, gosh.
(They quickly get in.)
Let's go.
(They're greatly advantaged if they navigate well.)
This car. It's pretty cute.
Do you have any money?
- Why? - Are you stealing from us?
(Eun Bi steals money as soon as they get in.)
What are you up to?
You're bullying us already?
You need money?
Can you buy me something at the drive-through here?
(McDonald's drive-through)
We have no time.
The destination is 45 minutes away by bus,
(She heard her Team Car...)
- and just 15 minutes by car. - Yes.
(could arrive 30 minutes before Team Bus.)
(Planning already)
- Yes. - We need that.
Okay!
Can you buy me something at the drive-through here?
We have no time.
What do you want?
Can you buy me an ice cream?
- You want ice cream? - Yes.
(Pleading with sparkling eyes)
- In the morning? - Yes.
She had silken tofu for breakfast.
- I had silken tofu stew. - What time...
- When did you have that? - Good for you.
(She gets a huge appetite ahead of her comeback.)
On the way here, in the car.
Well done.
Shall we go to the drive-through and get an ice cream each?
- Yes. - For real? Thank you.
- I'm so touched. - Okay.
(Trusting the extra 30 minutes, they head to McDonald's.)
Let's see. If we take a bus...
(Team Bus heads to the bus stop.)
Take a bus
Are you all right?
(Worried)
How was it? What did you think about my opening?
Do you want a score or what?
Give me a score.
It wasn't even worth one point.
- You can go slow. - I get better later on.
(The opening was miserable.)
- Take your time. - Okay.
- Running Man has lots of fans. - Yes.
- You must act natural. - Take your time.
(He's at it again.)
- Right, you can't. - You can't be too eager.
- Variety shows... - Right.
(The real Won Hun is still at it.)
You shouldn't try too hard.
- Talk when you're beside Seok Jin. - Okay.
- Seok Jin. - What?
How about we take a shuttle bus nearby?
- It's just a suggestion. - Sure, let's head over first.
- Let's check that. - We need a transportation card.
We must go to Gangseo Community Sports Center.
- Yes. - What's this?
Charge and use this.
(They get chargeable transportation cards.)
- It's the transportation card. - Five people...
(The money they have)
- Fifty dollars. - Won't ten dollars cover us all?
You can pay with one card.
A convenience store.
(Suddenly relaxed)
What a nice neighborhood.
There's a school zone.
- It's nice. - We don't have time to spare.
(It will take them 45 minutes even if they don't get lost.)
- We don't? - We need to win.
We can't run, though.
(Glaring)
From the start.
We must move fast and win.
Will the others take a taxi?
They'll drive.
(What are you talking about?)
- They got a car? - Yes.
(He understands the rules late again.)
Then we'll lose. Let's hurry.
We need to hurry.
- Do you have cash? - Say something.
Already?
- Of course. - Okay.
What a nice neighborhood.
(Being awkward)
There's a school zone.
We don't have time to spare.
(He made a pointless comment.)
- We don't? - We need to win.
- Nitpick whenever Seok Jin talks. - Okay.
(Do that instead.)
(Gulping)
Whatever he says. That's your mission today.
- If Seok Jin hits you, - Got it.
it's a good day.
- Shall I start now? - Keep on...
(Senior Yang secretly gives him a personal mission.)
Pick on Seok Jin.
Say things like you think he's wrong.
- I know the real you, Won Hun. - Yes.
(Real Won Hun)
You're polite and honest.
(Fake Won Hun)
Seok Jin dislikes that.
- You can pick on him. - I should be naughty.
Seok Jin, don't you ride the bus for free?
(Mission start)
Don't you ride the bus for free?
- In a few years. - Come here, you.
I will teach you...
You should teach him from the start. I have five more years.
- I had no idea. - How dare you?
- Hey. - He didn't know.
Let's hurry. He didn't know.
(He lets it slide for now.)
He might not have known, but...
(Satisfied)
- That was a good one. - It was a real misunderstanding.
Wait. Hyangdongsupnae Elementary School?
(Those at the front are navigating.)
(Cafe, outdoor stage)
This is... This neighborhood...
(Team Bus's current location, cafe, Susaek High School)
- I don't know it. - I'm not familiar with it.
Hang on. The transportation card...
(Looking around)
You can charge it at a convenience store.
(The convenience store)
- It's on the left. - A convenience store.
- Hello. - Thank you.
(They greet a friendly local.)
- Oh, dear. - The bike.
(Falling with a crash)
- Your bike. - Watch out.
- The bike. - Oh, dear.
(Won Hun joins in.)
- Watch out. - This is more important.
(He helps the local right away.)
- I wish you good health. - Thank you.
We need to cross now.
- We must cross. - It's fine.
- We have to go. - Cross the road.
(Thank you.)
Watch out.
- Hello. - Did you get it on camera?
My body reacted first.
I'm programmed to be polite and helpful.
- Won Hun, that was great. - Good.
(Securing screen time by doing a good deed)
Do that once more.
We can charge the card at the convenience store.
I should've refused the cash.
It's too late now.
(They're walking because they took 10 dollars.)
- Gosh. - Gosh.
We're disadvantaged.
But the first to arrive wins.
Yes.
- Don't state the obvious. - Okay.
Only what they'll broadcast.
There's an information board.
- Don't read everything. - Okay.
Are you older?
(Se Chan.)
- Yes, much older. - Much older?
(He is 3 years older.)
- He looks old. - He's younger than you think.
If Seok Jin hits you, it's a good day.
(The perfect time to get hit?)
Hey, you're still alive.
(He takes it.)
My eyes opened this morning.
- Seok Jin's flustered. - I'm nervous.
(He risks his life to complete the mission from Ssaebssaeb.)
This has never happened before.
- Seok Jin. - I woke up...
- Won Hun goes all the way. - I don't mind.
- He's direct. - I like comments like that.
(He's not done.)
I hope you survive the day.
- I always... - You were worried.
Let go of my hand.
- Stop it. - Don't stop me.
(He finally explodes.)
- Won Hun, you... - You started it.
- That's enough. - But he...
Hey, you... When did you start looking so old?
You look like you're my age.
- Stop it. - Let's be friends.
Seok Jin's serious now.
(Satisfied)
- Let's cross the road. - Let's go.
- Walk on. - We have to charge...
(The fake Won Hun brought out the real Seok Jin.)
the transportation card.
Charge the card.
- Let's charge it here. - I want a snack.
(They arrived at the convenience store without any bloodshed.)
- Charge... - Shall we get one?
- Yes. - Hello.
- Hello. - Let's be quick.
(Charging the cards.)
Can we charge our transportation card?
(They collect ten dollars from each person.)
- Use all the money. - Shall we use mine?
- Yes. - Okay.
The Blue Dragon award recipient will charge it.
Okay.
- Hello. - Hi.
I won the Blue Dragon Best Male Entertainer award.
(No one asked.)
Can you charge this too?
Thank you.
(They charge the entire 50 dollars...)
The bus stop is right here.
(that they got and head to the bus station.)
- Let's go. - Thank you.
Let's take the bus from here.
(Will they be able to find the way with just the map and bus route?)
- It's cooler in here. - Yes.
- Gosh, this place... - It's so cool in here.
- Let's take a look. - How nice.
Look at this.
(They check the route right away.)
Scan the routes.
We can go to MBC first.
- Yes. - Go to Sangam-dong first.
- Cross the road at Sangam-dong. - Yes.
- To go to Gangseo. - Yes.
(Team Bus's route: Head to Sangam)
Let's go to Sangam-dong from here.
(Change buses and cross Gayang Bridge)
From Sangam-dong,
we have to cross Gayang Bridge.
We can switch buses twice.
Sangam-dong.
(Let's see...)
This route...
- Jae Seok. - There's no direct route.
Let's take this bus.
(Susaek Station, Susaek Bridge)
- The 75A bus? - Eunpyeong Public Bus Garage?
- Bus garage? - Bus garage?
(They find a stop that's best for changing buses.)
- The 75A bus must stop here. - The 75A bus...
Let's get going.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
We take 75A and get off at the next stop.
- Okay. - After one stop,
get off at the bus garage, and take a bus to Gayang Bridge.
(The target bus arrives just then.)
That looks like the 75A bus.
You have sharp eyes. That's our bus.
- Where's the card? - I have it.
- Five people. - It's 75A, right?
(Team Bus gets a smooth start.)
Five get on first...
- I'll swipe at the end. - Okay.
- "Five people, please." - Okay.
"Five people."
Tell the driver there are five of us.
There are five of us. The last one will pay.
(Ssaebssaeb, who knows the area, takes the lead.)
- Won Hun. Get on. - There are five of us. Two, three,
four, five.
(Team Bus gets on their first bus.)
- It's done. - Okay. Thank you.
Hello.
I kept my bottle of water. What a nuisance.
- Shall I put it in my bag? - Yes.
(Kind)
- Do you mind? - Put it in here.
- Will it fit both? - Yes, I think so.
What a bother.
(Sudden change of tune)
- You mind? - No.
Did you blurt out how you actually felt?
(The fake Won Hun is kind yet unkind.)
No.
You two are quite chatty.
It's just that...
He has a bag too, but he asked me to put it in mine.
He offered to carry my bottled water.
Now he says it's a bother.
(He's enjoying teasing Seok Sam.)
- Have you ever gotten slapped... - It's one stop, right?
(Clenched teeth)
during a shoot?
- Not yet. - Not yet, right?
How does today sound?
- A bit later... - A bit later?
- This is a public space. - Yes.
- After we get off. - Okay.
(Getting angry)
(Well...)
Hello.
- Are you filming? - Yes.
(Local)
Hello.
I won the Blue Dragon Best Male Entertainer award.
Do you know his name?
- I do. - What is it?
(Local)
- Kim... - Kim?
- Won Ho? - Kim Won Ho.
- Won... - Won?
- Kim Won Ho. - Kim Won Ho.
(Blue Dragon award recipient Kim Won Ho)
- You're almost there. - Yes.
- Try a little harder. - Can I take a photo?
(Laughing)
- Won Ho. - Kim Won Ho.
(Trying again)
The Blue Dragon Best Male Entertainer award.
(Local)
I get that. Good for you.
Kim Won Ho.
- Poor you. - Thank you.
(Offers praise, not knowing his full name)
Good for you.
(Looks oddly pleased)
- Won Hun. - Hello.
Jee Seok Jin looks really young.
(Local)
- Seok Jin? She says you look young. - What?
I'm not that old.
He got stem cell injections.
(Suddenly)
- Yes... - You got younger.
(Local)
Thank you.
(Taking the opportunity to spread fake news)
- "You got younger." - Actually...
(It's not true, but the anti-aging treatment went well.)
Can you spread the word for me?
- Don't I look young? - Totally.
- He's 61. - Shut it.
He's really 61.
I'm not that old. I'm really not.
(Seok Sam 61 proves to the world that he looks young for his age.)
I see. We're taking a left here. We're almost there.
(Team Jae Seok)
- Jae Seok, we have to get off. - This is our stop.
(They arrive at the transfer stop.)
- Right here? - Yes.
- Take care. - Let's go. Thank you.
- Watch your joints as you get off. - Tap your card before getting off.
(Joking around)
Don't forget to tap your card.
Is this where we take the next bus?
(Scanning the bus routes)
- Okay, let's take a look. - Here.
Jae Seok. Hold on.
We have to go that way.
Straight down and to the right across the Gayang Bridge.
(Current location)
We need to make a right there.
(Following Navigation Yang, they cross the street to transfer.)
- That way? - Yes.
Here.
(All they have to do now is find the bus that goes across Gayang Bridge.)
Which bus do we need to take?
- Wait, check this one out. - From here...
Gayang.
(He found a bus that goes straight there.)
- Gayang. - Gayang Station.
- Does it go to Gayang? - Yes, Gayang.
(They'll cross Gayang Bridge to go to Gayang Station.)
Which bus is it?
It's 7602.
- It's a red bus. - Their intervals are long.
I know.
(They found the right bus stop, but the buses don't come often.)
This is bad.
They're going to get there...
- so fast. - Really?
They know they just need...
(Team Car)
- to cross Gayang Bridge. - Exactly.
I bet they've already crossed it.
Is it here already? There's our bus.
- It's here. - I think that's it.
- Wait. Get ready, guys. - Is that it?
- Because it's a red bus. - Express buses cost more.
(Luckily, the bus arrives right on time!)
- Is the fare higher? - Yes.
And we all need to sit...
(Team Bus catch another bus without a long wait.)
- in the seats. - Gayang Station.
There are 36 empty seats.
- The number shows up here. - The fare is higher.
Wait, it's 3.2 dollars. It's expensive.
- Shall we? - Go ahead.
- No one's a minor, right? - Five.
- Who could be a minor? - Two...
(What Seok Sam says is ridiculous.)
- Seok Jin, get a grip on yourself. - Three.
Is it free if you're 61?
(Won Ho is trying to save his big brother from paying the bus fare.)
- For 5 people, please. - It's not free even if you're 61.
What a bummer.
(Disappointed)
Seok Jin, here's a priority seat...
- for you. - Thanks.
Five people, please.
(They all get on the bus without anyone riding for free.)
Transfer.
- Hold on. This... - My gosh.
We need to watch the stops.
- Did you talk to the driver? - We need to cross Gayang Bridge.
(Their current destination is Gayang Station.)
Let's check after we cross Gayang Bridge.
It'll make a right here.
(Just trust me.)
You're right. There we go.
I think we can get off after we cross Gayang Bridge.
(Thanks to the bus arriving at just the right moment,)
(they're closing in on the other team.)
Straight forward. That's where we need to go.
(Meanwhile, Team Car is finally getting close to the bridge.)
We haven't crossed the river yet.
- Have we? - Not yet.
- Not yet? - Yes, go straight forward.
All right. Keep going straight.
We haven't crossed the bridge yet.
Is the river on the right or the left?
It's on both sides, dummy.
- Oh, right. - It's a bridge.
- Jong Kook, please. - Gosh, I'm sorry.
- I'm so sorry. - Was that necessary?
(A fool looking for only one side of the river)
- I didn't mean it like that. - But it's on the right here.
- That was a cute question. - But...
- "Which side is the river?" - Because of us...
She's holding the map upside down,
so the river's on the right.
(The map is upside down.)
Eun Bi, whenever you cross a bridge, you see the river on both sides.
(You have to look at the map this way.)
(Embarrassed)
- Because we're crossing the river. - It's all right.
- Left and right. - That's not what I meant.
- That was so cute. - A little thought goes a long way.
- It's all right. - So this is where we're going.
(Now, this is how you look at the map properly.)
That's it. We need to cross the bridge.
We're on our way from the cafe.
(Assistant Kwon isn't used to reading paper maps.)
- We've made it this far. - I see.
We might lose at this rate.
Anyway, we trust Eun Bi, so we'll let her guide us.
(She's off to a bad start.)
- Sure. - Okay, good.
Will we be crossing it soon?
Wait. I think this is Gayang Bridge.
That's right.
(They enter Gayang Bridge, with the river on both sides.)
- Yes, it is. - I'm right.
We're still staying on course.
- After we cross it... - After we cross it?
- We'll cross the bridge first. - Right.
(Kindly explaining again)
- We're almost there. - Not the 1st right, but the 2nd.
- Yes, the second. - Right.
Should we be looking for a drive-through place?
It's been a while since I was on the show.
Still, I'd understand if you hadn't eaten but...
(With 30 minutes to spare, she looks for a drive-through cafe.)
- Is the other team on its way? - Where is it?
- There can't be a direct bus. - Right.
I doubt there's a direct bus.
Is that so?
- Not here. - It's not this one,
(Team Car stops by a drive-through cafe without knowing the situation.)
- but the next one. - Right.
Wait. Where's the drive-through? I don't think they have that option.
Right here. On the left.
- Is it here? - Yes, go here.
(Following her lead,)
I can't believe you spotted that.
What are you getting?
(they arrive at a drive-through cafe.)
Well...
Bacon...
Ji Hyo, I thought you weren't getting anything.
(She feels hungry now.)
- I... - I want an egg McMuffin.
- And? - Jeju green mandarin McFizz for me.
And four Oreo McFlurries.
A box of chicken tenders.
(A massive order)
She wants chicken tenders.
- Would two pieces be okay? - Yes.
- Thank you. - Thank you. Take care.
(They get exactly what they wished for.)
(Nervous)
Are you sure this is allowed?
I think we'll still...
- get there first. - We'll probably win.
- Besides, - The map isn't very helpful.
I'm always lucky on Running Man.
- Right. - The other team...
(They can take it easy since they have a car of their own.)
probably has it rough.
They need to figure out which bus to take and then wait.
Hello.
- That looks so good. - How are you doing?
(Happily picking up their order)
- That looks good. - Thank you.
(Excited)
We need Eun Bi's drink.
- Excuse me. - Thank you.
Can we get some napkins...
- Napkins. - And wet wipes.
Can we get four wet wipes?
(Ordering more)
- Wet wipes, please. - Get two packets of ketchup.
They'd like two packets of ketchup.
This is definitely a first.
(Mr. Free Meals is happy about the quick snack break.)
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- Nice. - All set? Let's go.
- Come on, let's go! - Let's go, guys.
Let's go.
Deja deja vu
(Off they go, humming her song.)
That's it.
Wasn't there a famous song called "Deja Vu?"
(Taking a bite of a burger)
- There's a movie by that title. - Is it a movie?
(They're taking their time snacking in the morning.)
- There's a song too. - What?
- Really? - I'll keep yours here, Jong Kook.
All right. We need to make a U-turn.
- Yes, make a U-turn. - Right?
(Assistant Kwon takes a sip.)
Gosh, it's so good.
(Exclaiming)
- It's really good. - I know.
(Satisfied)
That's so cute.
It's so sweet and nice. This is insane.
(While Team Car comfortably leaves the drive-through,)
Seok Jin, I don't think we've crossed Gayang Bridge yet.
(Team Bus hasn't reached the bridge yet.)
Wait. We have to cross Gayang Bridge first.
We need to cross Gayang Bridge.
- Right. - We're doing just that.
- It's crossing the bridge. - It must circle back that way.
(They're finally crossing Gayang Bridge!)
- Here we go. - Okay.
- And then... - Yes?
After we cross Gayang Bridge,
(Team Jae Seok, Gayang Bridge)
we can get off two stops later.
(Will they catch up with Team Car, who are taking their time?)
If the bus turns right instead of going forward,
let's get off right away.
- Sure. - Okay, got it.
What do you say to a try-not-to-laugh challenge?
(Chuckling)
But you just laughed.
- You see... - Is it over then?
- This isn't a private bus. - Right.
Seok Jin, humor Won Hun, will you?
It's not that. He said that while chuckling.
(Superstar Jee is giving the newbie a hard time.)
I didn't know.
(Disappointed)
- I wasn't aware of the rules. - Humor him a little.
- I mean... - Variety shows aren't easy.
- He's a 30th-generation comedian. - What?
(Won Hun joined KBS as part of its 30th open recruitment class.)
- Are you from the 30th generation? - That's right.
- Isn't Jae Seok from the 7th? - He's from the 7th.
(KBS's 30th, 10th, and 7th recruitment classes)
I'm from the tenth.
- Tenth? - Along with Song Eun I...
(A 20-year difference between Won Hun and Seok Jin)
- and others. - He's a year above them.
Weren't the odds just 2 to 1...
back then?
Seok Sam wasn't a regular recruit.
- I'm a special recruit. - He's a special recruit.
- A special recruit? - He had connections.
Later on, he became part of the tenth generation of comedians.
(He's the only one who joined KBS through special recruitment.)
- He's a special recruit. - I'm a special recruit too.
(SBS's 8th special recruitment class)
Are you a special recruit? I should care for you more now.
- Now... - Only now?
(He starts caring about him after 10 years...)
Jae Seok, Seok Jin just hugged me.
(only because he found out he was a special recruit.)
- For the first time in ten years... - I should care more for him.
We're on a public bus. Please keep it down.
Haven't you done this before? We need to keep it down.
(The open-crecruit is keeping the special recruit in check.)
- Anyway... - There are other passengers.
(Glaring)
- Are you patronizing me? - Well, I'm the senior comedian.
(Worked up)
(He's got one ally, but he still can't stand up for himself.)
- I guess you're right. - Even as a special recruit,
you should respect him.
- I'm the senior comedian. - If you don't respect him,
(Calm down.)
- That's true. - Won Hun will disrespect me.
As a regular recruit, I know to keep quiet in public.
- I don't want to... - Because you're a regular recruit?
inconvenience anyone.
Special recruits talk a lot even in public places.
Special recruits, you say?
(He's preparing his next attack without talking back.)
I wasn't trying to disrespect you.
But regular recruits...
(Trying to attack)
- It's the opposite. - By the way, what's your job?
- Me? - Yes.
I haven't seen anything you've done.
(Targeting his popularity)
Seok Jin, what do you mainly do?
All sorts of things. I even have my own business.
Seok Jin, come on.
(He tried to attack, but ended up getting hit by his own arrow.)
You seem upset.
- You lost, Seok Jin. - What do you mean?
- You really lost. - Seok Jin.
(Let go of me.)
You're not helping yourself.
- Talk to me instead. - I currently do...
(Clenching his teeth)
- a lot of things. - You're good at what you do.
That's enough, guys. He might pass out from rage.
(After just a few words in,)
(and his blood pressure is already skyrocketing.)
- That's not it. - Stop it.
- He got on Seok Jin's nerves. - He got under Seok Jin's skin.
Anyway, what do you even do?
Right now, I'm on Running Man.
(Talking without hesitation)
- Seok Jin. - I'm not angry at all.
(Flapping)
- I'm not angry. - Don't you think...
- that's the same as being angry? - Is this a normal conversation?
I'm not angry. Look, I'm even smiling.
(A fake smile)
Take it slow, okay? We have all day.
I'm well aware that this is how he talks to people.
(He's figured out how to get on Seok Sam's nerves.)
He looks better on camera, doesn't he?
(The 2nd attempt)
- He looks better on camera. - Wait.
(He switches tactics and goes after his looks instead.)
- Are you making this personal? - That's not it.
I, for one, look better in person.
What are your thoughts on Seok Jin?
When I first saw you,
I thought...
I won't say anymore.
Seok Jin, you should take a break.
(Calm down.)
He's just making no sense.
- I mean... - Just take a break.
(He loses whenever he comes at someone.)
Everything he says...
- is so random. - Won Hun, look the other way.
- Seok Jin's... - It shouldn't be so random.
I bet it itches here.
(Scratching)
(He can't win the argument, so he resorts to force.)
Seok Jin, please. We're on a bus.
(Sighing)
- Won Hun, don't. - That's enough.
At this rate, you'll pass out from rage.
- Pace yourself. - But...
Seok Jin, I thought you were pretty decent.
Who scratches someone's head with a camera like that?
I stood up to applaud when you won a Blue Dragon Award.
I thought you were decent too.
I never asked you to.
I applauded you. You brat.
(He finally snapped.)
I mean... No, don't hold me back.
(A mess)
Pace yourself, Won Hun.
We should talk off the bus.
(Calling for a truce)
Right now, emotions are running high.
Wait, is it over there?
(Hitting)
(Truce negotiations break down.)
- No, it's past there. - I see.
We have to go straight down...
(The way these middle-aged men fight is embarrassing.)
- and make a turn. - I think it's that way.
You lost, Seok Jin. That's enough.
(His mic fell in all the chaos.)
Seok Jin, your mic. That's enough.
(A 20-year age gap couldn't dull their comedic chemistry.)
I want to switch teams.
Seok Jin, wait. There's a strand of hair.
- You and your makeup... - Check this out.
It caught some of Won Hun's hair.
Oh, no.
It caught some of your hair. Look.
(Hair, makeup)
- That's Won Hun's. - But...
(Seok Jin's camera)
- That's Won Hun's. - That's not cool.
(The camera shows signs of the battle.)
He got a hair transplant, you know.
- Really? - Exactly.
- He got a hair transplant. - I'm sorry.
- He plucked 4 strands. - I'll give you 10 dollars.
(4 strands of hair were plucked.)
I'll give you ten dollars.
- That's 30 cents a strand. - Isn't it 3 dollars?
You should say it's at least 50 dollars a strand.
(4 strands of hair)
- No, it's 3 dollars. - He planted 1,000.
Not 1,000. It's actually 4,000.
- Wait, 4,000? - That's a lot.
You must've been close to going bald.
- Yes, he was bald. - I see.
(The sketch ended with someone seeing blood.)
(Meanwhile, they almost crossed Gayang Bridge.)
We need to focus now.
Yes, we should focus.
Jae Seok, they can't make a right, so it'll go straight forward.
(Team Bus, Gangseo Community Sports Center)
- Right. - You can't make a right here.
Next stop, Gayang Station,
- Exit Eight. - We should get off.
(This stop is Gayang Station.)
- Here? - No, not here. If we do...
- Should we get off here? - Yes.
We'll get off and walk.
- Yes, we need to get off here. - Right.
- This is our stop. - Let's go.
- Let's go, guys. - Let's go.
(They get ready to get off at Gayang Station.)
Get off the bus.
- Thank you. - Okay, we're here.
(They got off the bus at a 10-minute walk from their destination.)
- Shouldn't we go that way? - Go straight ahead.
- Let's go. - I think so.
The McDonald's drive-through is here, so...
(Meanwhile, Team Car is 5 minutes away by car.)
Stop for a second right up there.
(They'll arrive sooner unless they get lose.)
Right. Here?
We should stop at the traffic light over there.
You have to turn right at the next traffic light.
- Should I turn right or... - Turn right?
(They follow Assistant Kwon's lead.)
will we find it if we keep going straight?
We turned down a side street to go to McDonald's.
Turn right here!
I don't think she's right.
- I don't think so. - I'm right!
- I... - Please, just this once!
- Listen to me. - Please, just this once!
- Please! Turn right here. - It's because...
- Let's listen to her. - Hurry.
(They could lost their lead at any moment.)
- Okay. I'll listen to you. - Okay.
Please trust me this once.
(They have to get there in one go.)
(Eun Bi is desperately trying to make up for it.)
This...
- This... - This...
(They decide to trust her and turn right.)
- No, trust me. - Okay.
We turned right here.
(Serious)
- "My thoughts could be wrong..." - I mean...
- I became so suspicious. - Me too.
(Confident)
We have to turn right as soon as we turn left from there.
- We have to turn right again? - Yes.
- Turn right? - As soon as we turn left.
(Firm)
- Let's trust Eun Bi. - Yes. Let's trust her.
(Despite their doubts,)
She said she's certain.
(they decide to turn left, then immediately right.)
Hold on. Turn right here.
- A right turn after a left turn. - Yes.
(He turns left first.)
Why do we see an apartment?
(They see an apartment complex entrance...)
- That's... - Are we entering the complex?
(right after making a left turn.)
That's not supposed to be here.
When should I turn right?
It's supposed to be here.
(She's flustered.)
Should I turn right at the next intersection?
(Loading)
The place we're looking for...
- Recalculating route. - is a concert venue.
- Is this the main road? - Yes.
Where are we?
(She's blank.)
(Neglecting the passenger-seat duties)
- Take a nap, Eun Bi. - Look over there.
That's where we came from.
(That's Gayang Bridge.)
- We're here. Right here. - That's right.
(She finally has an epiphany.)
That's right.
- That's right. - We were going like that, right?
- Yes. - For Eun Bi, the direction...
(They're going to turn right, then go straight.)
- changes when she turns the map. - That's what happened.
- That's what happened. - Now...
- After turning right, it goes back. - After turning right, it goes back.
(Gayang Bridge, concert venue, Kyungbok Business High School)
- Turn right. - Turn right.
How should you hold the map now?
I should hold it like this now.
- Because we're here. - That's right.
(Assistant Kwon gets the hang of it when they're almost there.)
- Yes. - Good job, Eun Bi.
- Like this. - It'll be on the right.
(Team Car will get there if they just head straight.)
- It will be on the right. - That's right.
Eureka.
Gangseo Community Sports Center?
(Team Bus starts walking as their destination is just ahead.)
- Let's go and... - Do we go straight?
Let's ask around.
Go straight!
(Gangseo Community Sports Center, outdoor concert venue)
- Straight? - Yes.
- Are you sure? - Yes.
(Navigation Yang is good at reading maps.)
Gangseo Community Sports Center.
If the intersection is here...
Were we supposed to go in between those earlier?
- Shall we turn in here? - Let's ask around now.
- This is the intersection. - Gangseo residents.
It's right here.
Do you know where the Gangseo Community Sports Center is?
It's somewhere around here, right?
(Over there!)
This way?
- Thank you. - Thank you.
We came to the right place.
(Things are going well for them.)
- We came to the right place. - This is the place.
(They even got some help from people.)
Shouldn't we start running?
- Now? - Yes.
We'll soon see Kyungbok.
(Team Car is looking for the high school near the destination.)
Kyungbok?
- Kyungbok Business High School. - That one?
- It's right here! - It's here!
(Outdoor concert venue, Kyungbok Business High School)
(They spot Kyungbok Business High School.)
- It's that one over there then. - That's the one?
- Should I turn right? - Yes. Make a right turn here.
- Make a turn. Okay. - Yes.
(If they turn right, they'll see their destination!)
- It's right next to this. - That's right.
- Make a right turn here. - A right turn here.
An outdoor performance venue.
(Keeping his eyes peeled)
It's an outdoor performance venue.
After a bit, we'll be seeing a performance venue.
(They're pretty much neck and neck.)
- I think we should make a right. - Kyungbok...
Even until the end...
It's right here!
(Did Team Car find the destination first?)
- It's right here. - It's right here.
It's here.
Where is the outdoor performance venue around here?
(Asking someone on the street)
(Team Bus is still on foot, asking for directions.)
Gangseo Community Sports Center.
- Turn right at the park! - The park.
(Go straight and turn right at the park!)
Turn right at the park.
(Enter)
- Thank you! - Turn right at the park.
They said turn right at the park.
(Passing the information on to Jae Seok, who is in the lead)
- Okay. - Okay.
- Over there... Seok Jin! - What is it?
- I guess it's this place. - Who is it?
- The park! - Is this the place?
(Team Bus spots their destination and starts running!)
- It's right here. - It's right here.
- We're here. - We're at the right place.
(Team Car is alos getting ready to get out.)
We found it.
It's right here.
(Their final destination is an outdoor concert venue.)
Is this the outdoor performance venue?
- It's right here. - I think we came first.
(The first team to pull out the flag wins.)
Hurry.
(Team Car was going a lot faster!)
- We have to hurry! - Eun Bi!
We have to run.
What is this?
(Team Bus caught the buses at the perfect time and never stopped!)
- Goodness. - Are they already here?
- Hurry! - We have to hurry.
(Which team will pull out the flag first?)
Run quickly!
- Run. - Run quickly!
We have to hurry!
Okay!
(Rolling)
Did we really win?
(Hollywood action)
- Won Hun. - Goodness.
- This is amazing. - We really won?
(Team Bus arrived first, which is unexpected.)
I didn't expect to win.
They're not here yet?
They aren't here.
- This is nice! - Nice!
(Those who stayed focused and came from behind to win!)
- Public transportation wins. - Amazing.
- It's hot. - Public transportation is amazing.
- Nice! - It's hot.
They're here!
(Team Car missed it by a hair.)
They're here.
- You're slow. - Did you just get here?
What happened?
Was it so hard?
(Trudging)
- When did you get here? - This makes no sense.
- We just got here. - Five minutes ago.
- Eun Bi... - Yes?
wanted us to go to a drive-thru.
Why would you go to a drive-thru?
(Their relaxed approach ended up costing them.)
- I'm full. - Did you eat?
- Really? - She even had ice cream.
She had ice cream.
(They're at least full.)
- That's what happened. - You had enough time.
It's like the tortoise and the hare.
(It's just like "The Tortoise and the Hare.")
That's why you're late.
Eun Bi is also...
bad at reading the map.
(Eun Bi's inability to read the map also contributed to their defeat.)
We won!
(Patting them out of awkwardness)
- Well done. - You know,
Seok Jin and Won Hun...
(The entire way here)
- have been bickering. - Are they using casual speech?
(Their love-hate brotherly dynamic was hilarious.)
Are they bickering?
- No. - He was specially recruited, and...
- I went through the regular one. - Seok Jin is so mad.
- Did you see me get mad? - He's very mad.
I wasn't mad.
You know our cameras, right?
- He used that to... - He hit his head.
- Was it that bad? - No.
- His hair got pulled out. - That's not what happened.
(Their bickering was so intense, he even lost some hair.)
- He hit him hard. - I just...
- It just went past him. - Don't...
(Reenacting for no reason)
Don't do that!
(The 2nd show begins for those who missed the 1st one.)
Why are they fighting?
He's been doing that for so long!
(Acting his heart out)
I'm holding back, you know!
Why did you do that?
(Their street fight looks so real.)
Why are you acting like this?
- Come here. - What's wrong with you?
(The comedian duo has perfect teamwork.)
He's really...
- What year did you join? - "What year did you join?"
(Bickering)
- Why are you fighting? - Why are you mentioning that now?
- Hold it in. - Hey.
- Are you joking? - It's just a joke.
- This is how we had fun. - They're joking.
It's a joke.
He's such a nice person.
He looks...
- a bit upset. - High five!
(Slapping)
He's joking.
(The love-hate couple's bickering comes to an end.)
- We're joking. - We're joking.
The winning Team Bus...
(A prize for Team Bus, the winning team)
- gets a prize. - What is it?
- Please show them the prize. - Will we get it now?
One, two, three!
(Luxury body wash and body cream, seasonal peaches, toilet paper)
Nice!
- That looks tasty! - What is that?
- What is that? - I...
(Luxury body wash and body cream)
- What is it? - There's body wash and cream too.
That's a good brand.
That's the one Se Chan took last time.
I'll take this today.
I was out of toilet paper. This is nice.
(Ssaebssaeb ran out of toilet paper.)
This is nice. I was out of toilet paper.
We'll decide the members...
- who get the prize. - Yes!
The winning Team Bus...
will choose either the blue button or the red button.
- Here's what's important. - This is difficult.
The member who picks the less popular option...
gets all the prizes.
If one person is in the minority,
- that person will take everything. - Everything?
There should be at least two members in each option.
If everyone chooses the same option,
you fail to get the prize.
They'll be carried over to the next round.
It's not easy to get a unanimous result.
- Eun Bi. - Yes?
I'll trust your gut feeling. What color should I choose?
- Red. - Okay.
I'll press that.
- I said that. - Okay.
I said I'll press the red button.
(Seok Jin plays mind games by saying he'll go with red.)
(Will he really choose the red button?)
(Pressing)
(Seok Jin chose the red button.)
I asked Eun Bi.
I said I'll trust her gut feeling and she told me to press red.
Everyone heard that.
I told them I'd press red and came here.
What will they think?
They'll think I'm going to press blue.
That's why I pressed red.
(Smug)
Those little punks.
(Odysseus Jee was thinking several moves ahead.)
(It's Won Hun's turn to choose.)
I have a feeling...
he didn't pick blue.
I have a feeling.
(Won Hun chose blue, unlike Seok Jin.)
(1 chose blue, and 1 chose red.)
I want those toilet papers.
(Se Chan pressed a button.)
(Whispering)
I'll choose...
(Thinking)
(Everyone has made their choice, including Jae Seok.)
The result...
is 4 to 1.
- There's no doubt. - Four to one?
- One person will get them all. - Who is it?
That was good.
(Red, Blue)
- That one person is... - Yes!
(Who will take all the prizes?)
Yu Jae Seok?
- Kim Won Hun, with blue. - Yes!
- That's amazing! - My instincts...
were spot on!
Everyone chose red?
(Everyone except Won Hun chose red.)
- That's amazing! - My instincts...
(Won Hun, the one who chose blue, takes all the prizes.)
- My instincts were spot on! - Everyone chose red?
They were really good.
I thought you'd all give it a twist.
Okay!
- But I'll... - I thought you'd give it a twist.
give up the prizes and become a regular on Running Man.
I won't take them.
Didn't you say that on "Hangout with Yoo?"
I think I fit in better here than on "Hangout with Yoo."
But how could you be the only one...
- Won Hun! - All of them?
I thought you'd give it a twist. Why didn't you?
I gave it two twists.
- I twisted your twisted decision. - I gave it two twists.
(Odysseus Jee's mind game confused them.)
- I twisted your twisted decision. - How nice.
- I should check if it's real. - That's amazing.
It's real.
Goodness.
(Jealous)
- There could be one more person. - Right.
- Yes. Let's move... - Thank you.
- to the next location. - Okay!
- Okay! - Okay.
(He heads to the next mission spot with his arms full of prizes.)
- Good job. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - That's amazing.
- Right here. - What is this place?
(The next mission will take place at a studio in Deungchon.)
It's really huge.
(A ball is placed on a large mat.)
- What is this? - What is this?
They drew a line.
I wonder what we'll be doing. Dodge ball?
I wonder.
(What's the next mission that is likely to be a test of strength?)
Hold on. This...
This mission...
puts both the prizes and the meal on the line.
It's called Lunch. Take it? Leave it?
(Mission 2: Lunch. Take it? Leave it?)
- What is it? - Take it? Leave it?
- Leave it, leave it. - Take it or leave it?
You'll play a 2-on-2 dodge ball match...
with each player tied to a player of the opposing team.
- Dodge ball? - Yes.
If you get hit by the ball thrown by the opposing team,
(Losing 1 point)
you lose one point.
You won't get eliminated.
You'll have three minutes per round.
You'll play three rounds, and the team...
- with the higher score wins. - Yes.
Okay. The winning team will receive a prize...
- and a hearty Korean meal. - Okay!
- I'm already jealous. I'm starving. - Okay!
The losing team will just eat rice with kimchi.
(That's the worst.)
- But you had McDonald's. - We already ate a lot.
(Team Car had McDonald's.)
- Did you eat something? - They had McDonald's.
Yes, they ate.
(Looking at him nervously)
- Seriously? - I'm starving.
I mean... Come on.
(Feeling betrayed)
We've already divided you into teams.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Se Chan, and Eun Bi.
(Team Orange: Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Se Chan, Eun Bi)
- Please stand together. - Sure.
Jae Seok, Seok Jin, and Eun Bi.
- That's right. - We've already won.
Haha, Won Hun, Jong Kook, Ye Eun, and Ji Hyo are a team.
(Team Pink: Won Hun, Ji Hyo, Jong Kook, Ye Eun, Haha)
- We've already won. - Won Hun's pretty sporty.
I'm pretty fast.
- You have no idea. - I'm pretty fast.
(Smug)
- Are you serious? - I'm quick on my feet.
- He's good at soccer. - I've got speed.
- Really? - He's really good.
These are the matchups for round one.
(Round 1 Matchups)
Jae Seok and Seok Jin versus Haha and Won Hun.
(Team Orange: Jae Seok, Seok Jin, Team Pink: Haha, Won Hun)
- Right, round one. - Got it.
- Okay. - Let's go!
- We've already won. - You'll put on your gear first.
(They put on team vests.)
- Sure. - Please wear your vests.
- Won Hun, can you get ours too? - Sure.
(Ignoring)
You didn't hear me.
Aren't you too young to lose your hearing?
- Already... - Here you go.
(He's still sore about what happened on the bus.)
- Thanks. - You must see him as a threat.
Seok Jin sees him as a threat.
Seok Jin...
Okay, nice.
I just like him, that's all.
(Smirking)
- I think it's one-sided. - For someone who likes him...
(The two rivals are tied together by a rope.)
- I mean... - So what will it be?
I don't want to shock him with my strength.
(Smirking)
Should I show a little respect?
I hate that. Why is that necessary?
(Annoyed)
- Should I do it for real then? - Sure.
(The mind game begins before the game even starts.)
- No holding back? - Of course.
Will this even work?
(Pulling)
Wait, he's pretty strong.
- I didn't... - He's strong.
- He's really strong. - I didn't even pull.
(Relaxed)
Seok Jin's really strong.
- He's on the heavier side. - That's right.
Seok Jin...
I see you're bad at catching.
Was that too sudden for you?
(Provoking)
The game hasn't really started.
- Yes, catch it like that. - Right.
(Catch it like I did.)
(The tension between them continues.)
Seok Jin, wait.
Seok Jin, what's the matter with you?
Hold on. I'll go next.
- Wait. - It's my turn, right?
It's not that. You should've caught it.
(Flustered)
- It's a practice round. - We're taking turns.
(Catch it!)
Don't you know what dodgeball is?
(Full force)
(Deadpan)
- Why are you going at it? - Won Hun.
He started it.
(Fuming)
- Seok Jin... - I was just warming up.
- It's not that. - Don't get into it.
(Calm down.)
- It's all right. - What's with them?
(He takes the ball before things get heated.)
Why are you getting into it with the kid?
We're not fighting. Kid? He's a full-grown man.
- I was just warming up. - Stop it.
You're going after him like you really mean it.
(Bickering again)
Haha, what do I do?
(Snapping the band)
- Won Hun, come on. - Won Hun.
- This is part of a long joke. - Of course.
(Don't misunderstand.)
- Back and forth. - This is how we joke around.
- Banter. - Banter.
(Their banter is as addictive as the smell of a belly button.)
- The ball will be in the middle. - Okay.
- Get ready. - Let's do this.
(The team that gets the ball 1st goes 1st.)
- Let's go! - Yes!
- Get ready... - The center.
- Go, team. - You've got this.
(Serious)
Run for it straight away.
(Round 1 begins!)
- Get it. - That's it.
- That's it. - Hold on.
- Okay. - I got it.
(Seok Jin kicks the ball and takes it.)
- What's wrong? - Wait.
(Team Orange is on the offense first.)
- Go. - Can you kick it?
Yes, that's allowed.
(He receives the ball and strikes.)
- Okay. - Yes!
(Losing 1 point)
(Team Orange: 0, Team Pink: Minus 1)
Haha, minus one point.
They can't attack anyway.
(Players outside the court can only pass, not attack.)
Pass it to me. That's it.
Wait, you're on our team.
(Team Orange is on the offense again.)
Keep passing it around. That's it.
(Holding tightly)
(Seok Jin's going to pull him close and then strike him.)
(Holding out)
What the... He's really strong.
(A little flustered)
Pass it to Jae Seok.
- Okay! - Pass it to Jae Seok.
(Throwing)
- What the... - Our team should get it.
- Come on. - Why on earth...
My arm was facing the wrong direction.
(He has the power, but not the accuracy.)
Yes. No, not yet.
- Don't. - Catch.
(Seok Jin intercepts the pass.)
- Nice. - Oh, no.
Seok Jin, pass it here and pull.
- I'll pull him closer. - Yes, pull Won Hun closer.
- I'll pull him closer. You hit him. - Good.
(Seok Jin will pull, and Jae Seok will throw.)
Catch it, Won Hun.
(Losing 1 point)
- Okay. - Okay.
- Get it. - Nice.
(Team Orange: 0, Team Pink: Minus 2)
(Won Hun collapses after getting hit with the ball.)
- Give it to me. - Ji Hyo, pass it here.
(No interest)
Hold on a second.
(In a rush)
Jae Seok, watch your back.
- What... - Nice.
- Nice. - Pass.
(Seok Jin blocks Haha's attack.)
- Pass it here. - Seok Sam's really good.
Pull him closer.
(Seok Jin's chance to attack)
Pass it to someone closer.
- I'll do it for real now. - Seok Jin's really strong.
- I'll do it for real. - Sure. Bring it!
(Won Hun's laughter fades after he sees Seok Sam's ability.)
(Starting to pull at full force)
- Wait, this is no joke. - Pass.
(Dragging)
- It's ours now. - Out.
What are you doing?
- It's ours now. - What are you doing?
- I mean... - What...
(He's already exhausted.)
- I... - He couldn't help it.
- What was that? - It's our ball.
- I lost my energy. - Give it here.
That's a turnover. Hand them the ball.
(Since he crossed the line, Team Pink gets the ball.)
A turnover?
Strike now. Make it fast.
- That's it! - Yes, strike fast.
(Losing 1 point)
(Team Orange: Minus 1, Team Pink: Minus 2)
Here. I'll serve him up.
- What... - Here. You almost have him.
(Power Seok Sam pulls Won Hun closer again.)
Here. You almost have him.
He's here.
(Losing 1 point)
That's it.
Hold on.
(Smug)
You're light work.
- Kim Won Hun, minus one point. - Yes!
Don't say my full name like that.
(Deadpan)
- Why not, Kim Won Hun? - Don't say my surname too.
(He got very sensitive after losing 2 points in a row.)
- But that's your name. - Just Won Hun.
(Team Orange: Minus 1, Team Pink: Minus 3)
Here you go.
(They're going at it again.)
(The old man still has some juice left.)
(Breathing out)
He's right here.
- Nice. - Good job.
(He caught it this time.)
- Pass it. - He caught it.
- Nice. - Good job.
(Serving absolute cringe)
- Nicely done. - Bring it. Just you and me.
(Bring it on.)
- I'll... - Pull him.
(Won Hun finally has a chance to attack.)
- I'll pull him and then hit him. - Okay.
I won't get pulled.
(Contrary to what he said, he's getting pulled closer.)
Hurry. Run forward.
Get him!
(His chance at revenge)
You've got it. That's it!
- What... - What was that?
- Seok Jin got you both. - What's wrong with you?
- Nice. - Haha, you got hit too.
- What... - What was that?
(Won Hun got taste of his own medicine.)
- Seok Jin got you both. - What's wrong with you?
- What was that? - Seok Jin got you both.
- Nice. - Haha, you got hit too.
What was that?
(Losing 1 point)
Seok Jin got you both.
(Losing 2 points)
It was a two-hit combo.
(A double strike)
(Time's up.)
- Round one is over. - Good job.
(Round 1 ends with a dramatic double strike.)
What are we going to do?
(It was a close game thanks to Seok Sam's strength.)
This is harder than it looks.
(Won Hun's drained of energy.)
The score is minus 5 to minus 1.
(Team Orange: Minus 1, Team Pink: Minus 5)
Team Orange is in the lead.
(Team Pink is 4 points behind.)
- This is bad. - Thanks.
What are we going to do?
(Team Pink: Jong Kook, Ye Eun, Team Orange: Se Chan, Eun Bi)
For the second round, pair up Jong Kook and Se Chan.
It'll be Eun Bi versus Ye Eun.
No way.
Eun Bi versus Ddochi sounds like a good one.
They're both pretty feeble.
- Eun Bi's on the stronger side. - You never know with Eun Bi.
- She lost some weight. - Exactly, I lost some weight.
(Eun Bi showed off her amazing core strength last time.)
(How will she do today?)
- Get ready for round two. - Got it.
(Round 2 begins.)
Ready...
- Get it. - Nice.
- There we go. - All right.
(Passing the ball, as expected from Soccer Kim)
(Team Pink is 4 points behind.)
Here. Hold this.
(Heave-ho)
He's getting dragged closer.
(Kim Muscles unleashes his monstrous strength right away.)
(Dragging)
He's getting dragged closer.
- Take that. What? - Hey.
(Losing 1 point)
(Paper Doll made an unnecessary move and ended up losing a point.)
- I... - Aim for his head.
That's what I aimed for.
- Nice. - Stay further back.
(Team Orange is on offense.)
- He went over the line. - I passed the ball.
You have to go over it completely.
Why is she so strong?
(Ye Eun is totally overpowering Eun Bi.)
Eun Bi, pull Ye Eun toward you.
- Pull her. That's it. - She won't budge.
She won't?
Just give it a try.
(Kim Muscles joins in.)
(Skipping)
Eun Bi, don't forget the ball.
(Eun Bi misses the ball and gets dragged.)
Eun Bi, where's your strength?
I must've lost too much weight.
(While Eun Bi lacks strength due to weight loss)
Run over there and... No, run over there.
(Se Chan is getting ready to attack.)
- I'll just hit Jong Kook. - Sure.
(Jong Kook lowers down and holds his ground.)
- Look at Ye Eun. - Ye Eun's gotten closer.
(Eun Bi is dragging Giant Gi.)
- Ye Eun's gotten closer. - There.
(Switching his target to Ye Eun)
Target Ye Eun.
(Don't you dare!)
(Flopping)
Nice.
There you go. Good.
(Losing 1 point)
(Losing 2 points)
(Team Orange: Minus 3, Team Pink: Minus 6)
Nice. Hit him again.
- Over here. - Got it.
(Finally, Se Chan grabs an opportunity.)
Take that!
(Losing 1 point)
And... Bring it!
Bring it!
(Ssaebssaeb is on a rampage.)
(Losing 2 points)
Take that!
(After scoring twice, he loses the ball.)
He aimed for Jong Kook's chest.
(It's my turn now.)
Get over here.
- Get over here. - Nice!
(Scared)
(Frantically backing away)
He got hit twice in a row.
- Hold tight. - Aim for Eun Bi.
(Jong Kook is enjoying messing with Se Chan.)
- For now... - Get him.
Take that!
(A hard slap to the face)
That hurts.
Give me a second chance.
(Kim Muscles teaches Ssaebssaeb a lesson.)
(He hits every target he can find.)
He got her.
(He narrows the gap.)
- Nice. - Score another one.
(Round 2 ends...)
(with them taking away the lead.)
- I'm exhausted. - We're...
(They went on an attacking spree at the end.)
- That was exhausting. - It really was.
- After the second round, - Yes.
(After Rounds 1 and 2,)
Team Orange has minus ten points...
while Team Pink has minus nine points.
- Team Pink is now in the lead. - Okay!
(Team Pink came from behind to win by just 1 point.)
- Thank you. - We're in the lead now.
- Did we lose? - What a relief.
- We're in the lead now. - Did we lose?
- No way. - By one point?
How about we play for real without the tethers?
- Without them? - I'm really fast on my feet,
- but the rope is holding me back. - It's unfair.
It'll be fun to play...
- without being tethered. - We need more players in the box.
Two per team will go in the box,
(For Swift Strike, who lost Round 1,)
while the others play from the sidelines.
(they'll play without straps in the final round.)
- You won't be tethered. - Not tethered? Got it.
(Hyping up)
- Make it look cool. - For real?
He's really good at this.
- Can I put my game face on? - Yes, do it.
- Not for entertainment but... - No, do it for real.
For the last round,
you may attack from outside the court.
- Really? - Okay.
- Then I'll be outside the court. - I'll be outside the court.
- Sure. - You should be inside the court.
You and Seok Sam will play inside the court.
(Seok Jin and Eun Bi from Team Orange will play.)
Ye Eun, you're too slow.
(Won Hun and Ye Eun from Team Pink will play.)
You've got slow hand-eye coordination.
- Ye Eun. - You're no better.
They're partners from "SNL."
- Ye Eun, let's do this. - Got it.
(Ye Eun and Won Hun, the Office Siblings)
- One, two, three. Let's go! - Let's go!
We have the Waterbomb Duo.
The Waterbomb Duo.
- One, two, three. Let's go! - Let's go!
(Seok Sam and Eun Bi, Waterbomb Father and Daughter)
- Get ready. - Step back a little.
(The final round for lunch)
Ready...
(Go)
(Swift Strike flies off at the sound of the whistle.)
- Hey. - Nice. Okay.
- That was great. - Nice one.
- I got it for us. - Let's pass it around.
(Trying to take credit)
- Target Eun Bi. - Nice.
(Thanks to him, Team Pink will attack first.)
- That's it. - Go for it right away.
- What are you doing? - Why didn't you aim at him?
- Nice. - Go for it right away.
(Tong Ki is just showing off. He isn't even attacking.)
- Go for it right away. - Why didn't you aim at him?
- What are you doing? - Why didn't you aim at him?
What's with him?
I'm just giving him a chance.
(Won Hun is full of bravado.)
Pass it around with Jae Seok.
(Team Orange is on offense.)
- Exhaust them a little. - Okay.
There. We can do this.
- Won Hun's fast on his feet. - Step a little forward. That's it.
- What the... - Nice!
(Ye Eun took it!)
Nice job, Ye Eun.
Ye Eun's good. Ye Eun!
(Eun Bi dodged it!)
- Nice one! - Se Chan.
Hey, Ye Eun!
(This is unusual.)
Nice one, Eun Bi!
(Without the straps, they're killing it.)
- Nice one, Eun Bi! - Keep the ball going.
(Both teams won't let their opponents win a score.)
Keep it going.
(Team Pink got the ball.)
Stay close, Won Hun.
Throw it close to you. Drain them out.
(Keep the ball moving!)
Drain them.
- Drain them. - Don't stay in the same spot.
(They play catch to drain the others.)
- Drain them. - Just take me out.
(Panting)
- That's it. - Just take me out.
That's it.
(Attacking when they're tired)
One more time.
(Team Orange: Minus 11, Team Pink: Minus 9)
- Drain them. - Attack right away.
Take someone out.
(Fake)
(Losing 1 point)
It was a hit.
- It's our ball. - Don't aim only for Eun Bi.
(He's even resorting to sneaky tactics now.)
- Us, too. - Ye Eun's too...
(Team Orange: Minus 12, Team Pink: Minus 9)
Play on.
Keep running about!
That's it.
(Seok Sam immediately fires back.)
- Gosh. - Is Ye Eun your only target?
- Move! - It's you.
- We got you! - Move!
(Won Hun let his guard down.)
We got you!
- We got you. - Half a point down.
(Team Orange: Minus 12, Team Pink: Minus 11)
(Just 1 point apart)
You're doing well!
Don't show your back, Jong Kook!
(Seok Jin caught Won Hun's ball.)
- Nice. - He caught it.
Take a short break, Seok Jin.
(Emergency)
- Rest. - Take a breather.
(Oh, no)
- Seok Jin... - Are you okay?
(He took the hit with a sensitive part of his body.)
Are you okay? Excuse us. Sorry.
(Pause due to an emergency)
(Administering first aid)
He doesn't need them. Who cares?
- He's fine. - He doesn't need them.
- They're out of service. - Yes.
- It's okay? - It's fine.
(He returns to the game.)
- Let's win. Let's eat! - Focus.
(On the other hand, Won Hun looks tired.)
I'm exhausted.
Won Hun's quick on his feet.
Seok Jin!
(Losing 1 point)
- Nice. - Nice one.
- Come on. - What a pity.
(Team Orange: Minus 12, Team Pink: Minus 12)
(He has recovered.)
It's a tie right now.
(It's a tie.)
- We're tied! - You're tied.
- We can win! - Looking good.
- Give me a chance. - Watch the time!
(Veteran Seok Sam is still going strong.)
- We're tied! - My pride is wounded.
Go. It's the last chance.
(They only have 30 seconds left.)
- Pass the ball. - Thirty seconds to go.
- Okay! Won Hun's out! - Get the ball.
(Losing 1 point)
- Okay! - Get the ball.
(The time is almost up.)
- Won Hun's out! - Okay. The last shot.
(Team Orange is 1 point ahead.)
Okay. The last shot.
- Catch it. - We're a point ahead!
Throw it anywhere.
(Team Pink has a chance to attack.)
- Be quick. - Defense!
- Come on! - Herd them.
- Herd them. Yes, good. - Throw it anywhere.
(If they keep holding out, Team Orange will win!)
- Now! - Catch it, and it's ours!
(Won Hun attacks!)
Catch it!
(What will happen?)
Now!
He caught it! Nice one!
- Well done! - Nice one, Seok Sam!
(Seok Sam halted the attack!)
Nice one, Seok Sam!
He's so good at catching!
(Acknowledging)
- Aim for the feet. - Go for the legs.
- It's over. - Nicely done!
- That was rough. - We won.
(Seok Sam's last-second save...)
- We came from behind. - At the end...
(helped Team Orange come from behind and win.)
- Good job catching the ball... - I managed somehow.
- Well done. - Nice one.
You're nothing, Won Hun.
(Down and out)
The final score is -12 to -13.
Team Orange won.
- Yes! - Okay.
- Nice. - Okay!
Seok Jin caught them all.
(Veteran Seok Sam did a great job.)
- You did great. - I'm so hot.
- Well done. - Nice teamwork.
Team Jae Seok won the game.
(He can't take it off by himself.)
The winning team gets a prize and a lovely meal.
(Team Orange has a chance to win food and prizes.)
Okay!
We'll show you the prizes first.
(What's the prize this time?)
- This is it. - The prizes are upgraded.
- What are they? - Premium honey.
- Honey. - Premium cinema tickets for two.
Freshly harvested corn.
The ball Won Hun threw earlier smashed the honey jar.
(A honey jar Won Hun broke?)
It's smashed?
(Before the game began)
Nice.
(Seok Jin and Won Hun played catch.)
(Smash!)
Won Hun...
(Won Hun threw a home run.)
- Sorry. I was warming up. - Don't go overboard, Won Hun.
Sorry. Was there something here?
(The honey jar cracked.)
- What was it? - It's fine. Don't worry.
We taped it back up.
(The broken jar has been temporarily put back together.)
- Because of me? - Will it be tape-flavored honey?
- Won Hun. - Did you save some of the honey?
(Feeling sorry)
- The contents are safe. - The honey's fine.
(Fortunately, everything inside the jar is fine.)
- It's just the jar. - It's smashed.
Movie tickets.
(Premium honey)
Strain the honey with a cloth before you eat any.
A cotton cloth. Strain it with that.
You people didn't think this through.
Don't put anything there if you know we're playing dodge ball.
(Serious)
You should've kept it...
(Calm down.)
- Well... - You chose wisely.
To decide who takes the prizes, you'll set off one by one...
- to vote. - Not again.
Is it red or blue again?
(Only a few members can win a prize.)
- Yes. - It's red or blue again.
There are four of you, so there might be an even split.
(If everyone picks the same color or it's 2-to-2 split,)
Then the prizes will get carried over.
(the prize will carry over to the next round.)
- They're carried over? - Jae Seok.
Let's give it to someone.
(Only 1 person can win the prize anyway.)
- Okay. - Give it to someone.
We need it to be 3 to 1.
- Let someone have it. - Me, you mean?
(Confident)
- Yes, you. - Great.
- I'll go red. - Blue.
- Okay. I'll go red. - I'll go red.
(They decide to help Eun Bi.)
- I'll pick blue. - Wait.
(Wait.)
Isn't this the office worker team from a long-ago episode?
- She betrayed us. - It was us three.
- It's the same three. - Yes.
(Coincidentally, all three of them have suffered at her hands.)
Eun Bi duped us.
- Eun Bi stabbed us in the back. - We're the three she duped.
- In Sangam-dong. - I'll go blue.
(She doesn't care.)
- Blue, okay. - Blue.
(Will their promise be kept?)
I brought all my sincerity with me.
I'll play honestly.
(Eun Bi chose blue as promised.)
Switching...
will only ruin it, so I'll stick to red.
(Seok Jin also chose red as promised.)
I chose red and lost earlier.
(Did Jae Seok and Se Chan keep their word?)
- I'll announce the result. - Okay!
- You each chose red or blue. - Yes.
Let it not be an even split.
We got a 3-to-1 result.
- Three to one? - Yes.
(Did they all help Eun Bi as promised?)
- Someone wins? - No way.
- The one to take the prizes. - There's a winner.
- That one person... - Who is it?
- Who is it? - What happened?
is Jee Seok Jin who chose red.
What?
- Jee Seok Jin who chose red. - What?
(It's Seok Jin, not Eun Bi?)
(What happened?)
- This is called know-how! - I thought too hard.
- I'll go next. You'll go? - Yes.
(Se Chan went after Eun Bi.)
I'll go red the whole day. No, wait.
There's a fingerprint.
(He notices a fingerprint on the button.)
(He thinks Eun Bi chose red and switches to blue.)
(Pondering)
(Jae Seok also chooses blue to pay for the past betrayal.)
- This is so shocking. - It's not about that.
- Gosh, Seok Sam... - Hey.
(The butterfly effect of her actions)
Seok Sam, I'm disappointed.
- Yes! - Seok Sam.
(Seok Jin got the prize thanks to that.)
- You. - Do you want to swap something?
You take the honey. You smashed the jar.
- Do you have anything nice? - Jo Malone.
I love Jo Malone too. Forget the hand wash.
(I can't give you that.)
(Luxury body wash, peaches, toilet paper)
The peaches.
- Okay. - Peaches are nice.
(They decide to exchange.)
Sure. I like peaches.
Could you give me a few peaches?
- What? - Can I have a few peaches?
(Mumbling)
Be quiet, you punk.
- Today, you're a bit too... - Seok Jin...
(ScrooGee is particularly cold toward Eun Bi.)
- Gosh. - Come on.
Eun Bi's charm isn't working.
- However much... - Eun Bi.
- Don't be upset. - However much science advances...
Don't be upset. It happens.
When it comes to Eun Bi, Seok Sam...
- Is he strict? - He still has a grudge.
(Holding a grudge)
You chose your prizes, so we'll head over to eat.
(Lunch awaits the winning team.)
- Okay! - Yes!
Okay. What's this?
(A feast, a humble meal)
My gosh.
(Dramatically different spreads)
It looks delicious.
- My gosh. - It looks so good.
(Envious)
What's that?
We shouldn't have had hamburgers.
(Excited)
This is a must.
- It looks good. - My gosh.
(Exclaiming)
- Gosh. - It's too much...
(Only the winning team can enjoy this.)
- for us. - It looks great.
For lunch today, you get spicy pollack soup.
(Spicy pollack soup)
- Okay. - It looks good.
It looks amazing.
- Squid bossam. - There's bossam too?
(Chewy squid bossam)
- Yes. - Braised fish roe and intestines...
(Spicy braised fish roe and intestines with naengmyeon)
and naengmyeon.
The winning team can enjoy their meal.
(A feast for the winners)
There's so much, it could be a team dinner.
Everything is good for you.
The losing team only gets rice and kimchi.
- Okay. - That's too drastic a difference.
(The losing team only have kimchi and rice.)
- No way. - It's just what I love.
I'm losing my mind right now!
(Teasing)
You really love this?
- You should've won, then. - This is amazing.
- The fish intestines. - The roe and intestines.
(Gulping)
- However, the advertiser... - Yes.
(Special request from the sponsor)
specially requested that Jae Seok and Jong Kook eat on camera.
(Jae Seok and Jong Kook must eat.)
Despite being on the losing team, Jong Kook...
(Jong Kook joins the other table to eat!)
- will get to eat. - It was a special request.
- Join us. - He must eat, then.
- Jong Kook. - Do you know how much I love that?
(No way.)
You must join us, Jong Kook.
Lots of people take meat as their main protein.
(Grinning)
- Fish is good for you. - It is.
What's really good is squid.
It's amazing.
- Squid is a gift from above. - These dishes...
Did the advertiser mention anyone else?
- No. - After Jae Seok and Jong Kook.
No.
I think this is a first.
Everyone at this table was at your concert.
- You're right. - Yes.
(Kim Jong Kook's 30th anniversary concert after-party)
- Eat all you want. - Thanks.
- Enjoy yourself. - I will.
It feels like it's my treat.
- If you do good... - It looks like...
a post-concert party.
(This is his concert after-party.)
Gosh, all this food...
- Shall I serve you some? - What should I eat first?
The pollack soup hits the spot!
The chopsticks...
You should have some of this.
It's packed with fish roe and intestines.
Fish roe and intestines...
(A generous amount)
Jong Kook! Look at this!
Wasn't this prepared by someone with 50 years experience?
Try the braised fish intestine with water parsley.
It's really...
- Just... - It's amazing.
Put some fish intestine on the water parsley and eat that.
(Water parsley is the best part of the dish.)
It looks so good.
I'd love to have some.
It looks amazing.
(Savoring)
That's my favorite.
Fish roe. This too.
(Roe)
It's protein.
(He acts cute for the sponsor.)
The broth...
- Try the squid. - It's just packed with food.
- I'll try the squid bossam. - The roe looks amazing.
- My gosh. - Oh, gosh...
(Squid)
Look at this!
(Bossam)
Their kimchi is the best!
(Kimchi)
- Look! - It really looks insane.
- This too. - Hey.
Squid, kimchi, meat. Triple layers.
That's the real deal.
The triple layers look so good.
(Eating)
Who wants fish roe?
This is great. It's a real team meal.
Jong Kook's post-concert meal.
- Jong Kook. - I love fish roe and intestines.
(Kim Jong Kook's 30th anniversary concert after-party)
(The gloomy siblings can't join the party.)
- You sang so well. - Thanks.
- It was great. - I had great fun.
- Yes, good. - It was incredible.
(The others only have rice.)
See, this...
This scene is killing me!
Haha can't start the day unless he has soup for breakfast.
For real?
Do I get a mouthful for a funny "gonee" acrostic poem?
- Yes. - Have a go.
(Try it.)
- Go. - Go get me some fish roe!
- Nee. - Neener, you punk!
(Turning frigid)
Won Hun, you need to slow down.
- Hey. - It looks like...
we expected too much of him.
That was too infuriating.
(Jae Seok motions for him to calm down.)
Won Hun, give us another acrostic poem.
(Eun Bi gives him another chance.)
- Which letters should I use? - P and M for "Pollack milt."
- P. - Pollack milt is
My favorite
- Milt. - My gosh, it's a beautiful day
You little...
(He ended up swearing.)
Well, Eun Bi asked for another one.
- I told you to take it slow. - Seriously.
- Eun Bi, can you make one? - What's wrong with you?
(Sure.)
She can make an acrostic poem. P.
(Passing the pressure on her)
Please stop.
- M. - Maybe your jokes are bad.
That was a good one, Eun Bi.
(Eun Bi crushes him with an acrostic poem.)
It was neat.
Well done.
(After the boisterous lunch,)
- I'm full. - Shall we get going?
- Let's go. - What will happen now?
(they head to the next location!)
What's this?
- This is... - My goodness.
(There's a mysterious machine.)
- What's this? - There is a machine.
- What's this? - What's this?
- What? - Isn't it a massager?
- Is it for hair removal? - I smell aromatic products.
(What's the next mission for the members after lunch?)
Is it for hair removal?
This mission is Massage, Take It or Leave It?
- What? - Take it or leave it?
(The original creator)
- Take it or leave it? - Microcurrent therapy...
that lifts the skin is on the line.
(A microcurrent therapy session is the prize.)
- That's incredible. - Microcurrent therapy.
- You once had the EMS therapy... - That's right.
(Microcurrent therapy is...)
- for the mission. - I remember that.
It hurt so much.
(It was this device!)
It's working.
Yes! I'll do anything you say!
(A frequent item on Running Man that brings energy to the show)
- Is he being serious? - That's his genuine reaction.
One person who wants to tighten his or her skin...
(It uses the same principle as the massage device.)
can experience the therapy.
(For a quick preview, only 1 person will get to try it.)
- Okay. - I hate such therapies.
EMS therapy hurt so badly.
- Ma'am. - There is a therapist.
- Welcome. - Hello.
(Today's microcurrent therapy expert)
(Microcurrent therapist, Kim Young Ae)
I want to try it.
- Try it. - Try it if that's what you want.
(All right)
(The scaredy-cat steps up, which is unusual.)
Ma'am, I'll experience the therapy.
- All right. Go ahead. - Go ahead.
- Seriously. - I volunteer.
I can't stand such therapies.
- It's scary. - I find it scary too.
- Please lift your feet. - Okay.
(Jae Seok will experience it.)
- It's for the electric currents. - That's right.
(He puts his feet on the pad.)
Put your feet on them.
(Her feet go on the pad as well.)
Will they get connected like "Avatar?"
(She delivers the currents through her body and hands.)
Can you feel the currents?
Through her body...
Is it coming through her body?
- Do your feet tingle? - Through her entire body?
(Amazed)
(Rubbing)
- I guess so. - What?
Ma'am, please don't do this.
I don't know how to react.
(Shy)
You need...
a few drops of aroma oil for this therapy to work.
(A few drops of aroma oil to calm the nerves)
He gets embarrassed very easily.
Please give him the strongest currents.
(Massaging)
- This is... - Jae Seok, does it tingle?
I can feel it.
- Does it tingle? - Can you feel the electricity?
(Did he feel the electricity?)
- I can feel it. - The electricity?
Electric currents come out of her body.
That doesn't make any sense.
Can you feel the currents?
Through her body...
- Can you feel it? - Can you feel the electricity?
(Amazed)
- I can feel them. - Can you feel the electricity?
- I can feel it. - Really? Can you feel it?
- No way. - How?
- She is like an electronic man. - What?
- Really? - Hey.
(Stomping his feet)
Hey.
- That doesn't make any sense. - Don't lie.
- Ma'am. - Electricity is coming out of her.
(Electricity is really coming out of her.)
- Ma'am, are you okay? - You're lying.
I'm serious.
You're lying.
That's it.
(The electric hands come up to his face.)
- Can you feel it? - My eyes...
What? How does it feel?
My eyes are twitching.
- You're lying. - I'm serious.
(They can't believe what they're seeing.)
He is lying.
- Your eyes? - This is incredible.
(When her hands touch his face,)
- Your eyes? - This is...
- Really? - This is...
(his eyes become glazed over.)
Is there pain?
How is it?
- Is there pain? - You're lying.
(Fascinated)
- Maybe it'll twist his mouth. - It's electronic.
- What? - The more you talk...
(The microcurrent makes his face twitch.)
- I think it'll twist his mouth. - Seriously.
- You're lying. - You're lying.
(Screaming)
No way.
Jae Seok, don't lie.
(Scared)
- There is no way you feel it. - It doesn't make any sense.
(Screaming)
- He is lying. - Jee Seok Jin.
The password of Jee Seok Jin's bank account.
- Jee Seok Jin. - Stop it.
Be quiet.
- Be quiet. - Jee Seok Jin.
(He's about to spill all the beans.)
- I can tell you the password. - Hush. Be quiet.
(Screaming)
- It's unbelievable. - The experience will end here.
(The preview is over.)
Okay.
(A mission will soon decide who gets the full experience.)
Exactly how does it work?
How does it feel?
- You feel the currents. - Really?
(Still feeling it)
This side of your face got lifted.
- Really? - It got lifted.
Your mouth got lifted.
(This side of his mouth is really lifting.)
She only worked on one side of my face.
You look a bit like...
- a fish on a hook. - Seriously.
She only lifted one side of my face.
Now, you'll have a mission...
for the microcurrent therapy.
- It's so fascinating. - You can touch it.
(Setting up)
- Isn't it fascinating? - So...
(Sneaking)
- is it safe? - Yes.
- It's safe. - Please take off your mask.
- My mask? What mask? - Yes.
Aren't you Pikachu in a human suit?
For goodness' sake.
Jae Seok!
She asked the therapist to take off her mask...
- and asked if she was Pikachu. - For goodness' sake.
- Hey. - Seriously, what's wrong with you?
(The man who tried too hard to be funny got apprehended.)
- Won Hun. - Yes?
(Won Hun, slow it down.)
- Okay. - Take it slow.
- I'll take it slow. - He keeps saying that.
- Take one step at a time. - Okay.
I'll take it slow.
(Until when?)
The mission for the massage is...
the Drawing Mafia.
(Mission 3: Drawing Mafia)
It's an individual event.
- Five people will go at a time. - An individual event?
- I see. - Mafia.
Each group will have one Mafia.
The rest will be civilians.
Once you get the keyword,
(Rabbit)
you'll take turns to draw for three seconds...
in order to complete a drawing that suits the keyword.
The Mafia will guess and draw without knowing what the keyword is.
Everyone will get two turns to draw.
If the Mafia succeeds in not getting caught...
(Rabbit)
or guessing the keyword, he or she will get two points.
(2 points)
If the civilians catch the Mafia...
(Arrested)
without revealing the keyword,
(Mouse)
(1 point)
- Team Civilians will get one point. - Yes.
- It'll be hard. - If you're bad at drawing...
(Worried about those who can't draw)
People will definitely suspect Jae Seok and me.
- No. Being bad at drawing... - I can't draw well either.
- gives you an advantage. - It gives you an advantage.
Here is the key point.
Even if you aren't the Mafia...
- You shouldn't make it obvious. - Right. You shouldn't give away...
(If your drawing is too good, the mafia might guess the keyword.)
- too many hints. - You can't draw a helicopter...
- even if that's the keyword. - You need to keep that in mind.
- You can't suspect all bad drawers. - You shouldn't make it too obvious.
Four members will receive...
(Only 4 people will get the microcurrent therapy.)
- the microcurrent therapy. - Four members?
- Four members? - Four members?
- Four members? - That's a lot.
(The intensity wasn't set high for the review.)
The setting wasn't high when she did it on me.
- If the setting is high... - Seriously.
I'm pretty sure it'll make me fart.
- I haven't used the restroom. - I'm about to fart.
- This is the first group. - Fart.
(First group)
Jae Seok, Jong Kook, Se Chan,
- Won Hun, and Ji Hyo. - Thank goodness.
Won Hun, don't try to be funny through this mission.
- I need to go slow. - That's right.
- That's right. - It's all about the teamwork.
- You need to enjoy yourself. - Running Man is...
(Won Hun, calm down.)
- my favorite show. Such games... - All right.
- Step by step. - That's right.
(Keep this in mind.)
- I won't try to stand out. - That's right.
(Telling himself)
I'll relax.
The categories for the keywords are...
proverbs, sports,
and book titles.
There are many categories.
- I like sports. - It'll be easy.
Here comes the keyword.
Will the Mafia get chosen at random?
(Only the mafia gets a blank sheet of paper instead of the keyword.)
That's how the game works. One person goes in blind.
Study each other's facial expressions.
Think beyond drawing well or not.
(Who is the mafia?)
The Mafia should be someone...
- who can't draw. - May I check the keyword?
Only one person got a different note.
(First keyword: You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge.)
This is what we need to draw, right?
How about the order? It'll be important.
- I'll go first. - Okay.
His confidence tells me...
- that he isn't the Mafia. - That's right.
- We'll need to see. - I volunteered for that reason.
(Is he an innocent citizen who is confident?)
- The Mafia will make it confusing. - You know...
Maybe it's his bravado.
(Is he a gutsy mafia?)
- No way. Who would do that? - Maybe it's his bravado.
- I'll draw. - Okay.
- Some people will know clearly. - Let's begin.
(Order of drawing)
One person won't have a clue.
- Let's begin. - Here I go.
This is for the first keyword. Get ready.
(Jong Kook volunteers to go 1st.)
Set.
(You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge.)
Ji Hyo is being...
- One, two, three. - No.
That's right.
(Did he only draw one straight line?)
- Draw right away. - What?
If you don't know what that is...
- All right. Look... - That's it.
Look into my eye.
Can you tell what it is?
- Of course. - Can you tell what it is?
(Nodding)
- You made it too obvious. - Can you tell what it is?
- I can tell what it is. - You gave too many hints.
- I don't think it's Jong Kook. - He doesn't seem like the Mafia.
(Won Hun is the 2nd one.)
- Won Hun. - One, two,
- three. Stop. - Won Hun.
Won Hun.
(He adds a figure on the straight line.)
- That's... - Won Hun.
I'm not the Mafia, right?
- Won Hun. - It's obvious, right?
- Take it slow. - Won Hun.
Don't give away too much.
I didn't give away that much.
- Hey. - Is it obvious?
Even if you aren't the Mafia,
(They have to draw subtly so the mafia doesn't figure it out.)
try to hide the keyword.
- Okay. - Otherwise, the Mafia will know.
- One, two, three. Stop. - My goodness.
(Ji Hyo goes 3rd.)
Ji Hyo.
(She adds a drawing on the opposite side.)
Gosh, this isn't good.
Ji Hyo isn't the Mafia.
(You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge.)
- This is... - Gosh, this isn't good.
Ji Hyo isn't the Mafia.
Gosh, this isn't good.
(The 4th one, Jae Seok, isn't confident.)
Ji Hyo isn't the Mafia.
It could be a proverb.
One, two, three. Stop.
(He adds a figure on the left side.)
- If you do that... - Hold on.
What?
- Jae Seok, that's... - That's...
(Suspicious)
It's too...
- That's... - What do you think?
It's Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok is the mafia.)
- If you do that... - Right now...
Is it a proverb?
(Is Jae Seok, who only drew limbs, the mafia?)
I guess they understand.
- I'll make it confusing. - Alright.
(Se Chan goes last.)
- You'll make it confusing? - Begin counting.
One, two, three.
- It's him. - What? What's that?
- Stop. - Okay.
What are those?
(3 stick figures appear.)
I'm not the Mafia.
(What he drew doesn't seem related to the keyword.)
Is it a proverb?
- He is very... - I had my intentions.
- He is very suspicious. - I mean...
(Doubting)
- The order... - I had my intentions.
(Se Chan looks very suspicious.)
Think about my intentions.
(Time for the second round)
- Okay. I won't give too many hints. - Okay.
One, two, three.
(Another straight line is added.)
- One person doesn't have a clue... - Won Hun.
about the keyword.
Won Hun.
It could be a proverb or...
I'm not sure.
- Stop. - Don't give away too much.
(He draws legs since they're a homophone for "Bridge.")
- One, two, - I think I know.
- three. - I think I know what it is.
- I think I know who the Mafia is. - Really?
(Ji Hyo adds angry expressions.)
- Jae Seok. - So we shouldn't give more hints.
(Next is Jae Seok.)
Set, go.
One, two, three.
- For goodness' sake. - Jae Seok.
Mister.
- Mister. - I mean...
(Jae Seok made it obvious they were enemies.)
- Jae Seok. - Are you helping out a colleague?
(You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge.)
I mean...
Isn't it "You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge?"
(Even the spectators figured out the answer.)
- A single-log bridge. - Se Chan, you're last.
- Because he is in Antenna... - So...
I shouldn't give away the keyword.
Go ahead.
- Go ahead. - I shouldn't, right?
- Go ahead. - Go ahead.
- Then... - Give us the hints.
(Se Chan, the prime suspect, goes last.)
Set, go.
One, two, three.
(He draws straps that aren't related to the keyword.)
- What? - So he was the Mafia.
- I mean... - Okay.
(Perplexed)
- Go ahead. - We got him.
- We got the Mafia. It's obvious. - We got him.
(We got the Mafia.)
- We got him. - We got him.
There was nothing else to draw.
(Is Se Chan really the Mafia?)
You'll choose the Mafia first.
Please pick the Mafia in the count of three.
One, two, three.
(Choosing the Mafia)
- Ssaebssaeb. - It's Se Chan.
(Se Chan is chosen.)
That's right. It's me.
(Confident)
- Se Chan is... - No.
- I'm not the Mafia. - Now...
- The Mafia. - He is the Mafia.
(They easily caught Mafia Se Chan.)
Mafia, please guess the keyword.
(If Se Chan figures out the keyword, he will win.)
This one?
- I know what it is. - Me too.
(You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge.)
I also know what it is.
(Will the Mafia, Se Chan, guess the keyword?)
Fencing.
Incorrect.
- Incorrect. - Come on. It's a proverb.
(For goodness' sake)
- What is it? - It's a proverb.
Isn't it a proverb?
You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge.
- Right? That was our guess. - We gave too many hints.
(Oh, right!)
We gave too many hints.
(He finally understands the drawing.)
- You meet your enemy... - Won Hun did that.
- I had the same guess. - They look like fencing swords.
(You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge.)
- That's right. - You drew the swords well.
- I see why he got fencing. - I thought the category was sports.
(The category)
- That's right. - I was so surprised...
- when Won Hun drew legs. - It was so annoying.
When Jong Kook drew a single line,
I got so annoyed.
I was like, "What am I supposed to do?"
(Detective Kook's straightforward strategy...)
And people were like, "That's it."
(that made Mafia Yang lose it.)
- I didn't know what to do. - Jong Kook did well.
I went first on purpose.
(Acting cocky)
Did you know it was "You meet your enemy on a single-log bridge?"
(An easy keyword that everyone got)
- We guessed correctly. - We guessed it.
- Right. You could guess it. - We guessed it.
(Bitter)
For the first question, everyone except for Se Chan...
(Jae Seok, Jong Kook, Ji Hyo, and Won Hun got 1 point.)
- got one point. - Okay.
- Yes. - Being the Mafia isn't easy.
The same group will play...
(Another round with the same members)
- the second round. - Okay.
- This is fun. - It isn't easy.
(Choosing the order for Round 2)
Which order do you want?
- What? - When do you want to go?
(Acting reckless)
I'll go first.
Oh, my. You didn't even get the slip yet.
(For his role)
- I know. I'm being brave. - That's how it goes.
- I'll go third. - Third.
(The order of drawing)
- I'll go fourth. - Fourth.
I'll go second.
- Then I'll go last. - Last.
I decided to go first before getting the slip.
If you're the Mafia, it'll be a disaster.
(What does Se Chan get?)
One more round.
It won't be easy for the Mafia.
(Heungboo and Nolboo)
It'll be very difficult.
(It's the keyword! Se Chan is a citizen.)
- Mix them up. - Isn't this too easy?
You know...
(Who will be the Mafia this time?)
All right.
This is...
(Giggling)
- This is... - I got this.
- Go. - Who is it?
- Who is going 1st? - You have 3 seconds each.
(Citizen Se Chan sets off first.)
I'm going first.
You'll be shocked when you see this.
- Okay. Go ahead. - Let's see.
Set, go.
- Ssaebssaeb. - One, two, three.
(He draws a gourd.)
- That's right. - It's a timetable.
- Not bad. - The second one.
- Two, three. - It's a timetable.
(It's a bluff.)
- Ji Hyo. - The second one.
(Second to go, Ji Hyo)
- All right. - Not bad.
Get ready. Set, go.
- You shouldn't give away the hints. - One, two...
- No, you shouldn't. - You shouldn't give away the hints.
(What?)
- Stop. - What? What's up with her?
(Heungboo and Nolboo)
Okay.
(Ji Hyo added a dot and lines on the gourd.)
This is suspicious.
- What's up with her? - All right.
Don't give away too many hints.
- I drew that for a reason. - Set, go.
(The gourd)
Don't give away too many hints.
- I drew that for a reason. - Don't give away too many hints.
(It's Jae Seok's turn.)
- One, two, - Come on.
- three. - No.
What are you doing?
(Jae Seok drew a stick figure again.)
- Another stick figure? - Well done.
I kept it a secret.
- I guess you didn't have a choice. - I couldn't give it away.
(Next, it's Won Hun.)
- I couldn't give it away. - Okay.
- Get ready. - I had to twist it.
- Two, three. - All right.
(Two lines he scribbled)
- Hold on. - What?
- What's up with him? - What?
I'm sure the civilians can figure it out.
What? He sounds so suspicious.
It's Won Hun.
(Mafia)
Jong Kook.
(It's Jong Kook's turn now.)
- Hold on. - I think I know what it is.
(Exhaling)
- What's up with him? - Don't you know the keyword?
- Don't you know it? - It isn't like that.
It's just that we need to do well,
(Awkward)
- so I'm thinking. - So what's the problem?
- Go ahead. - Show us.
(Mafia)
- I think it's Jong Kook. - The Mafia...
could figure it out.
(Kook Jong keeps stalling time.)
- Exactly. So go ahead. - So we need to make it obscure.
- Go. - Those words...
- Will it be okay? - Go.
- Will it be okay? - It'll be okay.
- I think it's Jong Kook. - I'll do it for real.
- Go. - I did that earlier.
No. I'll do it.
(Jong Kook exudes a strange vibe.)
- No. - I did that earlier.
- Go. - I'm serious.
I think Ji Hyo is the Mafia.
- Show us. - I'm not the Mafia.
- He is framing a civilian. - I didn't know he was so chatty.
- Get ready. Set, go. - I'll draw it at a distance.
(After stalling time...)
- He is the Mafia. - I'll draw it at a distance.
(He adds another stick figure.)
- All right. - Okay?
- Okay? - A person.
- Okay? - He drew a person.
(All of them had a turn.)
- It's hard to tell. - Okay?
- I'm not sure about Jong Kook. - All right.
I told you.
(It's Ji Hyo.)
It's hard to tell.
I'll draw something absurd to throw Ji Hyo off.
Go ahead.
(A random drawing that hides that it's Heungboo and Nolboo?)
Get ready. Set, go.
One, two, three.
- That's good. - I know what it is.
- Hold on a second. - I know what it is.
- Ji Hyo, you know what it is? - I know what it is.
(Ji Hyo even recognizes this random drawing.)
- You know what it is? - I know what it is.
(It's the prime suspect, Ji Hyo's turn.)
- Right now... - Set,
- You should know what it is. - Go.
- I guess it's a mushroom. - Stop.
(What is that?)
- What? - What is she doing?
- What's up with her? - I guess it's Ji Hyo.
(Mafia)
Is that Kumdori?
(Heungboo and Nolboo)
- Is it Ji Hyo? - It's a mushroom.
(What was Ji Hyo's intention?)
I'll draw something that's directly tied to the keyword.
(Jae Seok, who announced a big hint, goes next.)
- Give us a crucial one. - Hold on.
- Set, go. - It'll be dangerous.
Do it when we know who the Mafia is.
- Won Hun, why are you so quiet? - Yes?
I'll draw a crucial one this time.
(It's a swallow!)
- Stop. - I'll do that this time.
- This is... - You're an innocent civilian.
- My goodness. - Jae Seok.
- That's... - Jae Seok.
(Jae Seok drew the decisive character.)
- Don't do that. - That's a crucial one.
It's just lying there.
- That's... - You went too far with the hint.
That's right. I practically gave away...
(Next, it's Won Hun.)
- the keyword. - Won Hun.
- Give us something crucial. - Get ready.
- To that... - Set, go.
(Two lines again?)
- What's up with him? - What?
The civilians will understand.
- What's that? - Okay.
(What do the two lines that Won Hun drew mean?)
- The civilians will understand. - Okay.
- Go ahead. - All right. Hold on.
(Lastly, it's Jong Kook's turn.)
That's...
It's a crucial hint.
(He is suspicious.)
All right.
(Another suspect, Kim, keeps holding himself back.)
Jong Kook, there is no need to hesitate.
- Just give us a crucial one. - Get ready.
Here I go.
- Why is he hesitating? - Go ahead.
- Shall I get it right? - Set, go.
(Is he acting?)
Now...
Will you really draw that?
(He hasn't drawn anything yet.)
- Seriously. - We're onlookers.
We're talking to enjoy the show.
- What? Oh, no. - My goodness.
(Immersed)
- No. - Now, everyone will know.
Come on.
(Drawing a tiny circle)
- Stop. - What's that?
- Here. - Wait. That's suspicious.
- No. - He is the Mafia.
(Now, it's time for discussion.)
I'm 100 percent sure.
- It's Ji Hyo or Jong Kook. - Discuss it among yourselves.
(Mafia)
- I'm not the Mafia. - Ji Hyo isn't the Mafia.
(A citizen's opinion)
- You punk. - What?
(Pinching)
- What? - You punk.
- Me? - No.
He is the Mafia.
What are you doing?
(Cheek-pinching flirting out of the blue?)
Hey.
Are you trying to kiss me? What's going on?
(Tapping)
- This. - I see.
(Reenacting the spatula slap from Heungboo and Nolboo)
- Wait. - For goodness' sake.
(Jong Kook who slapped and Jae Seok who drew a swallow...)
- He knows the keyword. - That's right.
- Your drawing was fine too. - Of course.
(are ruled out as suspects.)
But Won Hun's drawing wasn't.
- I'm not the Mafia. - You...
- I made it obvious. - only drew two lines.
(Won Hun)
- What are those? - Can't you figure it out?
(Suddenly suspecting Won Hun who drew lines only)
All right. What Won Hun drew...
on his first turn tells me that he knows.
- That's right. I kept it subtle. - He knows the keyword.
(This is his proof as a citizen?)
Won Hun did that to not give any hints.
What is the meaning of this drawing by Ji Hyo?
She drew facial features...
- thinking that it was a face. - I agree with you.
Then she drew a mushroom.
Ji Hyo, why aren't you defending...
(Ji Hyo, who didn't recognize the gourd, is suspicious.)
- yourself? - I mean...
- I'm not the Mafia. - You aren't defending yourself.
- Seriously. - She is figuring out the keyword.
(The keyword)
She might get it right.
(Time to choose)
- One, two, three. - One, two, three.
- Ji Hyo. - It's her.
(Everyone chose Ji Hyo.)
- She won't guess the keyword. - I'm sure it's her.
I'll bet my entire fortune.
(Is the real Mafia hiding behind Ji Hyo?)
- I believe... - If you aren't the Mafia,
- you should've defended yourself. - Oh, my.
(Or is Ji Hyo the mafia?)
- Ji Hyo... - She just kept quiet.
- Maybe it's Won Hun. - Who is the Mafia?
- is... - You should've defended yourself.
- not the Mafia. - What?
It must be Won Hun!
- This is too much. - What?
(Who is the real culprit?)
- Is it Won Hun? - I drew the gourd.
- It's Won Hun. - See?
(Mafia Kim Won Hun)
- Three lines didn't make any sense. - Seriously.
- I'm not the Mafia. - It's Won Hun.
(Feigning innocence until the end)
- Hey. - I drew...
(Checking the drawing again)
I thought it was...
- a saw. - You thought it was a saw.
(Mistook what Won Hun drew as a saw)
- A saw. - A saw.
I thought the same,
- but this made me suspicious. - That's right.
(Se Chan intended to draw a gourd.)
- You drew a gourd, right? - That's right.
Is that a gourd?
I thought it was a face.
- What? - I thought it was a face.
- It's obviously a gourd. - It's a gourd.
(Ji Hyo's perspective)
Ji Hyo messed it up.
Why did you draw a mushroom?
- I drew grains of rice. - What's this?
(Ji Hyo's perspective)
- Grains of rice. - Are those grains of rice?
I thought it was a rice paddle.
- I thought he drew a rice paddle. - It's a rice paddle.
The Mafia, Won Hun, gets two points.
- Yes! - I'll get the penalty again.
- Seriously. - If you do well,
(You fool)
you won't get the microcurrent therapy.
- Won Hun. - You need to get the therapy.
(Oh, right...)
- He did too well. - You need to get the therapy.
(How frustrating!)
What's the use of winning this game?
(He becomes gloomy at the thought of being edited out.)
- You have a point. - Seok Sam.
- Yes? - Go ahead.
- We... - Give away the points.
If I get too many points, can't I get the therapy?
The fun one?
- Of course not. - Give away the points.
(Buddy...)
You might not be able to get it since you're ranked first.
(He's in the lead with 3 points.)
Won Hun, you're ranked first.
You're ranked first right now.
Gosh, Won Hun.
(Having mixed feelings, worried he might not have enough air time)
What's the point of ranking first?
You shouldn't have done so well.
- I mean... - What's the point of winning?
Why don't you have another round?
(Group 2)
That's right. Let Won Hun have another round.
(The older ones give him a chance to get more air time.)
- There are only four of us. - I got one keyword right.
- I'll try again. - Won Hun will join this round.
(Second Group)
- Play or lose, rock-paper-scissors. - Rock-paper-scissors.
- Go last. - Go first if you're brave enough.
- Go first. - Won Hun.
(Order of drawing)
- I'll go first. - Won Hun.
The Mafia will be chosen at random.
- We'll distribute the keyword. - The keyword...
- I'll draw without the keyword. - It's random.
The first one is hard. It's hard to figure it out.
(Laughing)
- Hey. Jae Seok. - Books or proverbs.
(Sharing it with everyone)
Won Hun was funny just now.
- What did he say? - "I'll draw without the keyword."
I'll draw before checking the keyword.
(Lying)
Books...
(Checking the keyword)
and proverbs.
Proverbs and sports.
That's right. Books and proverbs.
(The keyword is a proverb, sport, or book title.)
Don't give too many hints.
But this is too easy.
(Keyword)
Don't give too many hints.
(To the mafia)
- Ye Eun. - Her words are suspicious.
- Are you flustered? - Her words are suspicious.
- "Don't give too many hints." - Ye Eun...
- seems a bit flustered. - I know.
(Who is the spy this time?)
- Don't give too many hints. - It's suspicious.
- Don't draw the details. - Don't draw the details.
(Won Hun goes first.)
- Won Hun, you're first. Get ready. - Okay.
Set.
- One, two, three. - What?
Stop.
- Don't get greedy. - He is drawing a lot.
- What's that? - What's that?
What's that?
(What kind of animal is it?)
I got that drawing...
- from one word. - For goodness' sake.
- Come on. - Only the civilians will know.
(Next, it's Haha.)
- Get ready. Set, go. - I mean...
- I drew very well. - One, two,
- three. Stop. - What?
- What? Wait. - You'll understand.
(It's just the sun and a tree.)
- What's that? - You'll understand.
- I don't understand. - Are all of them...
- the Mafia? - What?
- You'll understand. - What?
(Super suspicious move)
- I'm serious. - No.
- Haha is the Mafia. - I'm serious.
(Mafia)
- Haha is the Mafia. - Why?
- Wait. That's... - It's unrelated to the keyword.
(Next, it's Eun Bi.)
- Go ahead and draw. - Perhaps he made it confusing.
- Eun Bi. - I told you.
- We need to fool the Mafia. - Set, go.
One, two...
- Stop. - No. Stop.
Stop.
- Only Haha didn't yell, "Stop." - It's...
Is it "Once you get startled by a turtle,"
"you can get startled by a cauldron lid?"
(Once you get startled by a turtle...)
(The audience got the answer after seeing a cauldron lid.)
- Three. Stop. - That's it.
- That's it. - A cauldron lid.
- Get ready. Set, go. - I think it's Haha.
(Seok Sam goes next.)
One, two, three.
Stop.
(He draws a big face.)
- I know what it is. - It looks a bit strange.
(Next, it's Ye Eun.)
- You know what it is, right? - Yes.
- Set, go. - The Mafia...
- You know the keyword. - Seok Jin,
(Adding a heart to the body?)
- make it hard for the Mafia. - Three.
We can answer right now.
- Set, go. - I'll make it obvious.
(It's Won Hun's turn again.)
Go ahead.
It's totally Haha.
(Indicating they're surprised)
- What's that? - That's right.
- That's right. - Haha.
(He just adds more strokes to Won Hun's drawing.)
It's Haha.
(He's the Mafia.)
- Make sure the Mafia doesn't know. - No...
(He adds something.)
- Seriously. It's not him. - It's him.
- Here! - It's Haha.
- Make sure the Mafia doesn't know. - No...
- Here! - Seriously.
- It's not Haha. - There!
(It's a turtle!)
- Now it has to be less obvious. - I know what it is.
(Haha seems to know the keyword.)
- What? - It's not me.
- Draw properly! - It's not me!
- It's not you. - It would've been obvious...
- if I drew that. - Okay.
- Don't say anything. - Be quiet!
Let's all play like pros. Darn it!
- Please. - People will suspect you.
- Haha figured it out later. - Hold on!
- He figured it out. - He figured it out.
(Is Haha a citizen or mafia?)
- What are you talking about? - He figured it out.
I drew that because you were suspecting me.
(Seok Sam adds eyeballs.)
- Hold on! - Look. You get it, right?
Eun Bi.
It's not me.
(Eun Bi adds eyelashes.)
- Eyelashes. - Eyelashes?
(Everyone is done drawing, with Ye Eun who added an eyeball.)
- You can't draw the same things. - Stop!
- Please discuss it. - I drew an eye.
(It's time to question.)
- You drew an eye? - I drew an eye.
It's either Won Hun or Haha.
(The mafia)
- It's not me. - Haha...
- It's one of the two. - Haha...
- suddenly... - He figured it out.
- Seok Jin. - But...
- I think Haha figured it out. - That's not true.
- That's not true. - Haha.
I'm curious. Why did you draw the flower?
(Once you get startled by a turtle,)
That's not a flower.
(you can get startled by a cauldron lid.)
- What is it? - Should I say it?
Whisper it to me.
- I can't do that. - Tell me.
It's not a flower?
- I think... - Seriously.
Haha figured it out after the first turn.
(Won Hun claims Haha realized the keyword...)
- That's not true! - At first,
(after a turn.)
- Won Hun! - the sun and the tree...
- I think it's Won Hun. - He's framing me.
- He drew the sun and the tree... - It's Won Hun!
- It's Won Hun. - What did I tell you before?
I said we should make sure...
(Haha claims he made the drawing confusing...)
- the Mafia doesn't find out. - The Mafia shouldn't find out.
- It's really not me. - I said it shouldn't be obvious.
(so the mafia wouldn't figure it out.)
- I'm sorry, but I'm confused. - What's that pig about?
Is this a pig, Won Hun? Why did you draw this?
(He's suspicious.)
He drew the pig's feelings.
(What's with her?)
- Eun Bi. - It's not the pig's feelings.
Why did you draw the pig?
- Why did you draw the pig? - Should I explain?
- It's Won Hun. - This is frustrating.
(Mafia)
- Everyone. - Why did you draw it?
- The pig... - It's tasty when it goes up here.
- He expressed the feelings. - It's tasty when it goes up here.
(Won Hun claims he drew a pig...)
- Is that why? - That's why I drew it.
(to express a cauldron lid indirectly.)
- That's why? - You get it now, right?
- Then... - The specialty restaurant?
(Like pork belly on a cauldron lid?)
- That's why? - You get it now, right?
- What's tasty? - The specialty restaurant?
(No idea)
It's not me.
- It's really not me. - It's Won Hun.
- I know. - It's Won Hun.
(Won Hun's excuse doesn't work on Ye Eun.)
This team made it so obvious.
I was the first person. How would I draw that?
- You're so bad at this. - Let's just proceed.
(Time to choose)
- Okay. - Pick the Mafia.
It's definitely Ye Eun!
It's not me! I'm serious!
(Suspect 1: Won Hun who drew a pig)
- Then... - It's Won Hun.
- One, two... - If it's not Ye Eun...
It's not Ye Eun.
(Suspect 2: Haha who drew nature)
- One, two, three. - It's Won Hun.
- Please point to the Mafia. - One, two, three!
- It's him. - Haha.
(Everyone chooses Won Hun.)
- He got lucky. - It's really Haha.
- He got lucky. - It's Won Hun.
- He's acting so well. - He's crazy.
(They both insist they're not mafia.)
- It's Haha! - Seriously.
- It's him. - It's Haha.
- We won. - It's Haha.
We won.
(Citizen)
I'll announce the Mafia.
- He's really giving me the chills! - Seriously!
- Hold on. Let's do it again. - It's not me.
(They start judging Won Hun.)
- Haha? - Okay.
Kim Won Hun...
(Is Won Hun the mafia?)
- It's Haha. - is...
- He's? - not the Mafia.
- That's right. - It's not him.
- It's not me. - It's not Won Hun.
(He was serious about pork belly on a cauldron lid.)
- He drew well. - He drew on top of that...
- That's right. - Right.
(Who's the real culprit that fooled everyone?)
- It's not me. - The Mafia...
- is Haha. - That's right.
(Mafia Haha)
It's so obvious.
- This doesn't make sense. - Why didn't you pick him?
(Nature)
He figured it out in the middle when we drew this.
- Eun Bi! - The cauldron lid was a mistake.
- I was this one. - This shouldn't have been drawn.
(Cauldron lid)
- This gave it away. - Ye Eun!
(The mafia realized the keyword because of Eun Bi's cauldron lid.)
Who drew this?
- It was Haha. - Eun Bi drew that.
- You shouldn't draw that. - We shouldn't draw such things.
- That's how the Mafias get it. - It's so...
(In the next round, they succeeded in catching Eun Bi.)
As a result, Eun Bi is in last place.
(The final result)
- In last place. - Right.
Se Chan came next.
You two will get the microcurrent therapy.
- Okay! - Try it out.
- We have to pick two more people. - Yes.
Eun Bi, who's in last place, will decide.
Well...
Seok Jin could...
- Seok Sam. - Hey!
(Fluttering)
Stop that! Why did you pick me?
(Choosing the eldest so he could regain his strength.)
- Let's go! - Why do you always...
- drag me around? - Seok Jin will get it.
(Who is the last one?)
Pick one more person.
Kim Won Hun.
- Kim Won Hun... - Kim Won Hun.
(Won Hun is chosen.)
Kim Won Hun will get it.
This still happens even though I did well in the game?
(Secretly feeling happy)
- Of course. - That's how life is.
I'm not sure I can make people laugh with that.
(Time for microcurrent therapy)
- Seriously. - I sit here...
- Yes. - This is correct, right?
(The first guest is Won Hun.)
You can place it there.
- Won Hun. - Is it wet?
- Yes? - This is the last one.
This is the last scene.
- This one? - Yes.
Are you saying I should do something here?
Just experience it.
Let's keep it natural.
- Right. Keep it natural. - Don't overdo it.
- Hello. - Hello.
Please take off that mask.
(Laughing)
What was that?
(Making a fake comment right away)
He's crazy.
Won Hun...
(Calm down)
Please raise your hand if it hurts.
(Right then, the therapy begins.)
- It could be bad too. - Goodness.
- He's rolling his eyes back. - Won Hun!
Won Hun! That's fake!
It's unbelievable!
(Gleaming)
It's not that strong.
- Hey. - That's too much!
You tried it earlier.
- I'm serious. - Won Hun!
Hold on! It's too strong!
(Going overboard with his reaction to secure his air time)
- It's too strong. - It's not strong.
Hold on. It's so...
Should I make it less intense?
(Making a fuss and heartfelt reaction)
No!
- This much... - This much...
(Grunting)
I thought he got shot just now.
I cried. Goodness.
(The audience is super satisfied.)
- Your face looks better. - But...
(He's become prettier.)
- What? - This part got pulled up.
Could you do it on my neck again?
(Being a pro)
- This side? - Yes.
(Laughing)
(An encore performance)
(Succeeded in performing with Pikachu)
He looks possessed.
That's fine.
(He's going third.)
- Okay. - It's scary.
How could you make her pick?
(Scared)
- Won Hun! - I did my best!
(It's Eun Bi's turn.)
- Go and sit. - Seok Jin.
- Seok Sam. - I wasn't overreacting.
- It's tough. - Go and sit.
- Is it Eun Bi's turn? - I wasn't overreacting.
(Lying)
You saw Won Hun do it, right?
- I think she'll take it well. - Eun Bi.
(The micro current is on.)
Is it okay? How is it?
How is it?
But since she's skinny...
- Does it feel bad? - She's doing the waves.
(Eun Bi takes it well, unlike someone.)
That's the feeling.
It's that bad? It's like a magic show.
- But this is... - A dermatology magic show.
This place is flickering.
What?
(What is she saying?)
- That's right. - Which place?
- Is that true? - Yes.
- It flickers like this. - That's not good.
(Agreeing)
- Your mind is going blank. - The lights are flickering.
(It feels like this.)
- That's right. - Really?
Doesn't it hurt?
It doesn't hurt.
(Eun Bi is enjoying it.)
- She's fine now... - She's enduring it.
- Are you enduring it? - Women endure it well.
- They endure it well. - They endure it better than men.
Eun Bi is enjoying it.
It feels a bit refreshing.
Yes. It's refreshing. You look prettier.
The color is coming back to her face.
(Eun Bi is done with the experience.)
- She really looks pretty. - Next is Seok Jin.
- He had his glasses on. - I had them on.
(It's Seok Sam's turn.)
I'm strong, you know.
- It didn't start yet. - It didn't start.
- I didn't start yet. - Seok Jin!
- You should place your feet. - Place your feet there.
- Place your feet there. - Place them there.
(Screaming)
- Come on. Seriously. - Come on.
(Here's an oldie who is being overly dramatic.)
- Come on! - I'm serious!
- Goodness. - Stop faking it.
- It shocks you! - Just roll your eyes back.
- He's being too much. - Come on.
(Screaming)
- What was that? - Place your feet there.
This part is getting fried.
(Making a fuss)
- Put your feet there. - You'll become prettier.
What's wrong with you?
(In falsetto)
He's lost it.
(Seok Sam has lost it.)
- Please, ma'am... - Jee Seok Jin!
How much do you have in your bank account?
(Starting a skit)
I have 25,000 dollars.
(Suspected to be a secret account)
Spill it quickly.
What's your bank account password?
It's zero...
(The account password)
(Right then, a DJ passing by enters.)
I thought he was a DJ.
(Screaming)
Why did you raise that?
(DJ Yu played with a dial that was unrelated.)
Hey!
- One side went up. - Did my eye become bigger?
- Let's see. It got pulled up. - It's true!
- Goodness. - Seok Jin!
- It went up? - Your eye went up!
(He succeeded in going back to his 50s.)
- This side... - It got pulled up.
- I can't see myself. - It went up.
Yang Se Chan.
She's pulling it above his back.
(Se Chan will get it while lying down.)
- Se Chan. - His belly is really...
(An electric current is flowing through his back.)
- His belly looks cute. - It's like a baby's belly.
You're supposed to get it while lying down.
I don't feel the electricity.
It's coming!
(She starts rubbing his neck.)
- She's... - I want to bring it to him.
- She's... - Mother!
(Even the jawline)
Hold on.
His belly button is dry.
(Calm down)
Won Hun.
(Forcing it)
You should do it with him. Do this, Won Hun.
You're touching him.
(Groaning)
Hold on. It's coming to me as well!
(Won Hun's show is back.)
(Calm again)
(The customer squirms from getting the belly therapy.)
- It hurts! - Really?
- Hold his feet. - Hold his feet.
Hold his feet.
(Exclaiming)
(Top-notch overacting from a musical theater major)
(The finale)
(The current therapy that produced a lot of air time is done.)
Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
The final choice that decides when you leave work.
(The last choice, the end of today's race)
It's called Get off work. Take it? Leave it?
- Let's go. - This is the real one.
- We should take this. - Okay.
You'll pick either the blue button or the red button.
(As expected, there are 2 buttons.)
- The minority will get to leave. - Really?
The members who pick the less popular option...
- will leave work right away. - Okay.
The members who pick the popular option...
will leave work after getting the penalty.
This is worth trying.
Please move one at a time.
(Jae Seok enters first.)
I'm having the worst luck today.
(The 1st choice: Red)
It's Kim Won Hun who chose blue.
(Fail)
(The 2nd choice: Blue)
It's Jee Seok Jin who chose red.
(Fail)
(Will he be able to laugh at the last minute?)
- This is really hard. - Won Hun.
This is the last one.
- The final choice. - Go, Won Hun.
- Go, Won Hun. - Go.
You have to pull it off here.
Here?
- Go, Won Hun. - I'm not sure...
which one I should press.
Slow down.
Should I press it slowly?
- Yes. Take your time. - Slowly.
He's in a rush.
Haha has ruined...
so many people like this before they even got to bloom.
- Watch out for Haha. - Right.
(Making Haha a star doesn't have a nice ending.)
- When Haha finds something funny... - Exactly.
When Haha finds something funny...
My gut feeling is insanely good.
(Won Hun is done choosing.)
So I rarely ever get caught in these penalties.
(The rest of them are done making their choices.)
I'm just going to leave it all up to fate.
Please!
- I'll now announce the results. - The results!
The results! The minority.
Tell us the breakdown first.
(They'll avoid getting the penalty only if they're in the minority.)
- All right. - Is it 5 to 4?
- There are nine of you here. - Yes.
(The ratio of red and blue is...)
- What's the breakdown? - Is it 6 to 3?
- I bet it's 7 to 2. - Is it 6 to 3?
- It's 5 to 4. - It's 6 to 3.
- It's 6 to 3. - My goodness.
Is it 6 to 3?
I think I'm getting the penalty.
Only three of us get to go home.
(Only 3 people can go home.)
The three will go home right away.
I was thinking about changing my choice.
The color for the six people who get the penalty is...
(Muttering)
(Red is getting the penalty.)
It's red!
(Jae Seok,)
- I knew it. - Red?
(Ji Hyo,)
Red? It's the three of us!
(and Seok Sam survived because they pressed the blue button.)
Ji Hyo, Seok Jin, and Jae Seok.
They will go home without getting a penalty.
Haha, Jong Kook, Ye Eun,
Eun Bi, Se Chan, and Won Hun...
will get the penalty before going home.
I was thinking about choosing red.
(The 3 who survived)
It's been weeks.
(He's been getting the penalty for weeks.)
We will bring in today's penalty.
(Revealing today's penalty)
I'm so happy.
What is it?
Today's penalty is...
making a rubbing print of your face...
- with a custom-made ink sponge. - It's simple.
Pull your hair back.
This is the last one.
- All right. - Can we pool it onto one person?
- That sounds good. - Pool them all?
(A suggestion by an airtime master)
- Deal. - I'm in.
- Let's do that. - Pool them all onto one person.
- Two. - Two of you will be out.
(They decide to excuse just 2 people.)
So this is another chance.
This is why people survive on mere hope.
I know.
- Take one each. - Pass them out.
(Giving out an O and an X)
- I'll give these out. - Please!
(4 people with O get the penalty, and 2 people with X survive.)
All right.
We don't know how it will turn out.
- Thank you for the good one. - Please.
I prefer getting what I'm given.
- Me too. - This is...
- One by one... - Wait. Is this a number?
- No. It's O and X. - It's O and X.
If it's an O...
(The penalty)
So you got an O.
If you get an X, you survive.
(Revealing Jong Kook's first)
- Jong Kook goes first. - Jong Kook.
One, two, three.
(He got the penalty.)
- O. - Okay.
The odds just went up.
(Broadcasting)
- Eun Bi. - One, two, three.
X.
(Eun Bi was excused.)
- I can't believe this. - Eun Bi.
(Only 1 out of 4 can survive now.)
- Just do it. - Now...
It's 25 percent.
- One, two, three. - Let's just do it.
Okay.
(Ye Eun gets the penalty.)
- It's 33 percent. - Now there's 1 spot left.
- Isn't it two? - One, two, three.
(Se Chan gets the penalty.)
- It's 50 percent! - It's 50-50.
- At the same time. - It's 50 percent.
(Who is the lucky person between Haha and Won Hun?)
Won Hun should do this.
One, two, three!
- Yes! - Okay!
(Kim Won Hun)
(The 2 guests are excused!)
- I did it! - Won Hun should do this.
- You have to do this. - Won Hun.
- Seriously, Won Hun should do this. - He has to.
We should do it again.
- The two guests... - Won Hun has to do it.
- The two guests can't get away. - You have to do it.
- This doesn't make sense. - Let's do it again.
- Won Hun has to do it. - Right.
The two guests are exempted,
(Calm)
and the rest of the members will get the penalty.
- All right. - Won Hun lost his solo shot again.
- It could've been fun. - We prepared a lot for him.
(Tsk, tsk)
- I feel bad for Won Hun. - We will wrap it up...
after hearing the two guests' final remarks.
Eun Bi and Won Hun did a great job today.
(It doesn't feel right.)
Eun Bi's new song is "Dejavu."
Yes. I'm back with "Dejavu."
(The summer queen's thoughts after she returned)
Please enjoy my new song a lot.
I was so happy to be here today.
Thank you!
- All right. - Okay.
Won Hun. You did well today.
(Next, it's Won Hun's turn to share his thoughts.)
Yes.
I had a lot of fun today.
I'll see you next week.
(Calm down.)
I mean, I will...
- I'll see you around. - That's it. See you around.
- I'll see you again. - Okay.
(When will Won Hun's next time be?)
- Good. - Thank you.
(Right after that, Se Chan, Jong Kook, and Haha...)
(successfully made face rubbings of their faces.)
- That's it. - It will look good.
(Last to go, Ye Eun)
It looks like a sheet mask.
(Commenting when he can)
It looks good. It's round.
(It even duplicated her eyes that scream, "Unfair.")
- It turned out really well. - It looks good.
(All 4 of them complete taking the penalty.)
Ye Eun looks like Bodhidharma now.
Ye Eun's rubbing looks good.
Thank you for today.
(Thanks to Won Hun and Eun Bi for the amazing laughs in the heat.)
- Thank you. - Thank you.
- It's Kyeong Hwan. - Where are you popping up from?
(To tighten up the members' slack discipline,)
(the best guests are gathered together.)
- You punk. - You punk.
(Chaotic from the very entrance)
(Lee Ju Yeon, Heo Kyeong Hwan, MIYEON)
- Hey, MIYEON. - You should go.
The three of you are the same height.
(Great chemistry where they even matched their heights)
- I'm wearing heels. - We matched our heights.
I'm being considerate of the ladies.
(A pathetic excuse)
(Unconventional)
That dance...
(The ace guests push forward with sheer momentum.)
That's good!
The dance... Ye Eun...
(And Paper Doll plays along.)
(As expected, it's not easy to fight against the regulars.)
This is it.
(Strict)
It's too late. Do it again.
- Please, sir! - I can't believe this.
(Endless blocking and interference from the regulars)
- I got it. Ten Longevity Symbols. - No.
(Launching straight into an unexpected stunt)
(When you're a little upset...)
- Hang on. - The question is strange.
(Chaos)
Stop it.
- Please delete it. - Just blur it.
(Calm)
There's no way I can get it right.
(It makes zero sense.)
What's that?
(If you can't land a blow, survive by any means necessary.)
Next.
(Nonchalant)
(A crisis for a 19-year veteran comedian)
- Let me answer. - I said I wouldn't do this.
(Entrenched regulars versus fresh intruders)
- Good. - This is amazing.
(Who will be the protagonist to live a brand-new life?)
(Undisputable AI Pick)
Jae Seok! This is it!
(Running Man)